From time immemorial,
the ancient Ukrainian forest
has harboured amazing secrets
and mysteries.
Behind the Dark Mountain,
in the forest's heart,
the Source of Life is hidden.
It provides the forest
and its dwellers
with their power, their spark.
But one winter,
while the forest
was fast asleep,
with the guardian alone
watching over it,
a human broke into the forest
through the passage
in the Dark Mountain.
It was the owner of the sawmill.
He needed at least one drop
from the Source of Life
to save his dying
newborn daughter.
But then he returned
and brought an army with him,
hoping to take over
the entire Source for himself.
And so a terrible battle began
that left no winners.
Only losers.
All humans who had trespassed
behind the Dark Mountain
vanished.
The Forest Guardian
lost all but an echo
of his ancient strength.
And when the forest creatures
woke in the spring,
they were greeted by
the horrific consequences
of the humans' treachery.
Look at what
our enemies have done.
For this reason,
no human shall set foot
behind the Dark Mountain
ever again!
This is the new forest law.
Many years have passed
since that day.
Another winter is over.
Oh, I've slept so long.
I was having
the loveliest dream.
But this is better
than any dream.
It's finally spring.
Swampy!
It's the best part
of the best day of the year.
Time to wake up the forest.
Hark! Hush, the master
of sounds, approaches.
Happy spring, Mavka!
Hush! You can fly?!
That's kind of huge news.
They'll call me Hush,
who conquered the sky!
Just don't tell Lesh.
He'll think
I'm stork-raving mad.
Whoa!
Yeah! One more! More!
And the fans go wild!
We are so ready
to conquer the world.
Settle down, kid.
Hometown crowd.
Everybody knows us here.
Wow, I'm just so nervous.
What if things don't work out
in the city?
There are so many
other musicians there.
You have to believe
in yourself, Nina,
and let the music
show us the way.
Whatever that's
supposed to mean.
What was that?
"Big money
for an important job?"
Hm, not for a soon-to-be
musical legend like me.
But maybe Uncle Leo
can use this.
Lucas, your uncle,
he's not feeling well.
They called the healer
and everything.
Get home, quick.
Hopefully we'll see you
at the fair later.
-Hey, look!
-What is it?
Greetings,
after so long,
my dear fellow villagers.
It is I, Kylina,
the daughter and only heiress
of the late sawmill owner.
The one that got burned up
by forest demons?
Yes, my father died tragically
in a forest wildfire,
but it had nothing to do
with your quaint superstitions.
After dear Daddy's death,
my mother and I left this place,
but soon I became an orphan.
-Oh, poor thing. What a shame.
How positively tragic!
But now I am back to make
our village prosperous again.
I'm offering you all a job.
You'll have so much money
that you'll never
have to work again.
Not working is my dream job.
I'll rebuild the sawmill.
We'll start selling our timber
all around the world.
Aren't you all good and ready
to become rich and happy?
-Yeah!
-Absolutely.
-Yes!
-What do you want us to do?
All you have to do is pop over
the Dark Mountain...
What?
Oh, she's cuckoo.
Ugh, just like her father.
But I'm talking huge money.
You can't buy another life.
Tell the evil spirits I said hi.
-What's that?
Easy, easy.
What's the matter?
A trap!
Probably left
from the old times.
Huh?
The guardian is calling us.
Uh, how is he?
He's holding on, but my herbs
can only do so much.
Leo needs real medicine
from the city.
But...it's not going
to be cheap.
Uh...
"Per-du-cabri-co-carum"?
Just give this to the pharmacist
in the city.
He'll understand.
Thank you. Sincerely.
Great news, Uncle.
A little perdi-caca-something-um
and you'll be good as new.
Lucas, what are you doing?
You can't waste
your money on me.
I'm old and I've had
a good long run.
Spend it on a nice girl,
get settled down...
..so your old uncle
can die in peace.
Nobody's going to D-word.
I'll find the money
some...where.
Uncle, you'll be fine.
I've got you.
-I've got you!
Oh, madam,
it's your family mansion.
How...rustic.
Ugh, it's just
a revolting hovel.
A bunch of pathetic cowards!
All my plans are at risk
just because this primitive mob
is terrified by the forest.
-Move it, Frol!
Oh, ma'am. Right away.
Just a second.
Do me a favour and get
these peasant rags off me.
How can they wear
this hideous stuff?!
Ugh, I hate it.
Get rid of it right away.
What a terrible piece
of tasteless trash.
Stupid, uneducated,
superstitious mob.
-Frol!
-Oh, my God.
This is so old-fashioned.
Don't get me upset, Frol.
It's bad for my complexion.
Oh, sure, madam.
-Oh!
Clumsy idiots!
Inside this case is...
Just be careful with it.
Mm?
What is it?
Uh, about this job offer...
Oh, forget it.
Who's there?
Frol!
Oh, about THAT job offer?
Please come in.
Hi. My name's Lucas.
It says you'll pay well.
Hmm.
I will.
If you're up to it.
Uh, I am.
I can do any job.
Good.
Eric, Derek, you go with him.
So...what do I have to do?
Find me the tree with this leaf.
Uh... Huh!
In the forest
behind the Dark Mountain.
Hmm.
FOREST-DWELLER: What happened?
The guardian
is summoning everybody?
This hasn't happened
since I was a sapling.
-I'd rather take a nap.
-The guardian?!
Greetings upon the new spring,
my fellow forest-dwellers.
Is everyone here?
Mavka, did you wake
everybody up?
She's probably frolicking
through the crocuses
with Swampy again.
-I'm sorry I'm late, Guardian.
I was helping the lynx cub
get out of an old trap.
-How terrible!
-An old trap.
I thought they were
all removed after the battle?
Nymphs.
You are
the forest's armed forces.
Which one of you missed this?
Good job, Mavka.
You've embarrassed us
in front of the guardian.
Now, then,
listen, forest-dwellers.
The Supreme Spirits of Nature
whisper that dangerous times
approach.
Therefore, at midnight tonight,
in the heart of the forest,
the spirits shall choose
a new guardian.
Lesh, but what about you?
I have so little strength left.
The guardian's burden
has grown too heavy for me.
Lesh won't be
the guardian anymore?
Will the humans attack us again?
-Who else can protect us?
Hark.
Hush the sky conqueror
can become the guardian.
Guardian chatterbox?
Yeah, just what we need.
I heard that.
But really, anyone
can become the guardian.
You mean like even you?
No, no, no, Mavka.
You may be the sweet,
pure soul of the forest,
but for this job
you are just way too nice.
No, I'm not.
Ooh. I feel unwell.
Ondina, are you alright?
See? So gullible and nice!
Enough!
All will be decided at midnight
in the heart of the forest.
People say that
behind the Dark Mountain,
the water nymphs and tree
spirits can tickle you to death.
Uh, you're laughing and laughing
and then bleugh!
We don't believe in monsters
of the forest.
Where do we go from here?
I think through this way.
Uh...
Uh-huh.
I didn't think we came here
to hunt.
This isn't hunting.
This is fun.
-Yeah.
Impossible.
Today of all days.
It was an accident. I tripped.
I am extremely clumsy.
My childhood nickname was
Clumsy Lucas.
We'll make you
Clumsy Black-and-Blue-cus.
Mm-hm.
My brother thinks
you should go on by yourself.
If you find the tree,
mark it on the map.
OK.
I was gonna suggest that anyway.
I feel their fear.
Quiet down.
Everything is fine now.
What scared you so much?
Humans? Here?
I have to tell the nymphs.
Wait.
Come on, Swampy.
I'll deal
with the humans myself.
Let's show them how 'nice' I am.
Argh!
Where in the haunted heck
is this tree?
Believe in yourself, Lucas.
Let the music show you the way.
Whatever that means.
Ohh!
It's so beautiful.
Oh, thanks. I...
Uhh...
Argh!
-Argh!
Forest demon!
Argh!
Is the human dead?
Is this some sort
of human magic?
Mavka!
A lot of weird, whistly,
raspy sounds
coming from this exact area
and I...
-Uh, Hush.
You already learned
how to dismount the stork.
Nice.
I am on high alert.
Our forest has just been
incursion-ated by...
Argh! THE HUMANS!
I'll watch him.
You go get the nymphs.
Oh, no.
I say we can drive the human
out of the forest on our own.
So I would be Hush, the first
kicker-outer of humans?
Oh, I like that very much.
-Argh!
Uh... Argh! Evil spirits.
Keep back, I'm warning you.
I... I'm a...borscht belt
in combat polka.
Pathetic little human!
You violated
our sacred forest...
Huh?!
..and tried to harm
these noble bison.
No! Super no.
That was the bouncer brothers.
In fact, I saved
the bison from them!
What is this, then?
Oh. That's my flute.
I, uh, play my music on it...
with it.
'Music'?
And you were doing this
to try and magically
enchant me in some way?
No! Well, sure.
Music is kind of magic, but...
Wait, so you liked it, then?
You do not question me,
little human!
Why have you trespassed here?
A strange lady offered me a big
reward to find a special leaf.
Aha! You hear that? A reward!
I knew that all humans
were selfish and greedy!
-Why you little...
-Ouch.
You see this!
Human treachery!
Huh?
Wow!
You are the most amazingly
beautiful demon
I have ever seen.
Your eyes.
I am not a demon.
I am Mavka,
the soul of the forest.
Well, I'm Lucas.
The soul of...myself?
Look, I can explain.
I need that reward to buy
medicine for my uncle Leo.
No. I have been warned that
humans are skilful liars.
You have broken the law
of the forest and I expel you!
No expulsion necessary.
I'll leave myself.
Just let me find
this silly leaf first
or else my uncle...
..dies.
How awful. I'm so sorry.
-Whargh!
Hey there, little...
What are you?
This is Swampy,
the last of the kittyfrogs.
Awww!
It's so cute how much
he hates me.
-Oh!
You want something super yummy?
Had a feeling you'd like that.
You're very different
from the evil humans
in all the forest legends.
-Huh?
Huh?
Derek, hold my boomstick.
Derek?
Derek? Where are you?
I'll teach you,
you filthy human!
Hush, what are you doing?
Swampy, spit it out immediately!
This grotty fleshbag
is trying to poison you.
Hey! It's my mother's recipe.
Oh, Mommy
poisons folks too, huh?
Hush, stop!
Lucas, leave him alone.
-Huh?
-You gave it a name already?
Lucas. Stop it right now!
Well, he started it.
He has to leave.
I need the leaf.
Fine, here's a leaf. Now leave.
Not this one.
Are all humans this picky?
Lucas. It's not the leaves
you really need.
You need to heal your uncle
and I'll give you
the cure he needs.
Really?!
Oh, thank you. You are so nice.
Hey, hey, hey.
Do you really want
to break the law
to help a human on such a day?
You heard him.
He saved the bison,
and for some reason...
I believe him.
-Urgh!
After all,
the soul of the forest
must help all the living
creatures in the forest, right?
And Lucas is a living creature
who is in the forest.
-Huh?
-Therefore, I have to help him.
And you will help me help him.
Me?
No way! Never!
Never, never, never, never,
never, never, never!
-No!
When will I learn that I'm
incapable of saying no to you?
Don't worry, Hush. We'll make it
before the ceremony starts.
I'll give Lucas the cure
for his uncle and...
And then he'll leave
the forest forever.
I promise.
Hmm?
Come to me!
Don't be shy. Come closer.
Ahhh!
Huh?
Argh!
How did I...
Curses!
-Uh...
Oh.
Mm.
Huh?
Mavka, how can I thank you
for your help?
Just tell me and I'll do it
with pleasure.
Maybe you could play
your music for me?
Oh. Sure thing.
No, no, no, not now.
Nobody can know you're here.
No, let him play.
The nymphs will hide him
safely in the forest,
one piece here,
one piece there.
♪ Wonder, I pray
♪ The star you trace
♪ Here is our land
♪ Only tightly hold my hand
♪ Ask me
and I'll tell... ♪
-♪ How in love I fell
♪ Flying, flying
♪ Keep flying with me
♪ My world, your world
♪ No, we do not need the words
♪ Two hearts but one history
♪ Always beat in harmony
♪ My world, your world
♪ Flash of everlasting love
♪ Two hearts but one history
♪ Always beat in harmony
♪ Talking, talking,
talking to the wind
♪ Talking, talking, talking
to the wind
♪ Talking, talking,
talking to the wind... ♪
♪ Learn the language
♪ Of wind and rain
♪ Listen, listen
♪ To know me well
♪ Cherish your will
♪ Your song, your magic skill
♪ Keep flying with me
♪ My world, your world
♪ No, we do not need the words
♪ Two hearts but one history
♪ Always beat in harmony
♪ Talking, talking,
talking to the wind
♪ Talking, talking, talking... ♪
You know, humans are not
actually as terrible
as you've been taught.
We have a lot of nice things.
Like music. It's so lovely.
You must be the guardian
of music in your world.
Not yet.
But my dream is to fill
my whole life with music.
As soon as my uncle gets better,
my musician friends and I are
leaving for the big city.
"The big city".
What is the big city?
It's a place where everything
is made of bricks and stone
and there are as many buildings
as there are trees
in the forest...
Hurry up, hurry up. Move!
What are you doing?
Back off, shrubby.
Hush! Mavka!
Are you the ones
making all this noise?
Too late.
Nice knowing you, Mavka.
Up until today, anyway.
Lesh, how's it going?
Busier than I'd like.
Who is your guest?
Uh, I'm...Hush's...cousin.
Yes, dropped by
for a visit from overseas.
Right, Hush?
Uh-huh.
A very, very
many-times-removed cousin.
Shmucas is his name.
Ah! Welcome, friend Shmucas.
Come quickly.
The ceremony is about to begin.
Oh, great. What do we do now?
Do you realise how illegal
this is?
We just need to keep our
distance from the new guardian.
As soon as the ceremony is over,
I'll come up with something.
You look just like
your parents, madam.
Hm, much better now.
Yeah. Lovely portrait.
Totally...horridness.
Hmm?
Hmm. Did you find the tree?
So what stopped you?
Bunnies? Squirrels?
The forest demons?
Knuckleheads.
Totally useless. Oh!
Stop being such fools.
You are stupid idiots.
What am I paying you for?
And where is the boy?
Oh!
-Out of my way.
Oh, damn!
I'm running out of time.
And where is this peasant loser?
Ohhh! Oh!
-Hey.
Shhh!
It is time.
Hmm!
Oh! That's the...
The Supreme Spirits of Nature,
I summon you.
The One Who Dwells in the Earth,
I call on you.
The One Who Moves the Waters,
The One Who Flies
with the Wind...
..the One Who Sits
on the Rock...
..I call on you.
Those who protect us,
those who help us,
those who dwell
at the Source of Life,
please choose the new guardian.
Mm.
Hmm?
The guardian is chosen.
Huh?
-Her?
-Me?
What's happening?
Is it good or bad?
Please close the knothole
on the front of your face.
Lesh, why me?
I can't possibly be
the guardian.
I have to tell you something.
The Supreme Spirits are wise,
and they know who is capable
of protecting our realm.
Now the Supreme Spirits
will bestow their powers
on the chosen one.
-Incredible.
-Perfect.
So how do we "keep our distance
from the new guardian" now?
Mavka, you are now granted
the powers of
the Supreme Spirits of Nature.
It is for you now
to always remember
that our enemy -
the humans - are out there.
Defend this fragile,
sacred place
with your very life.
Please welcome our new guardian
of the Source of Life
and the forest.
That was just...whoa!
Our little Mavka
is now the guardian.
I always knew this would happen.
There has got
to be some mistake.
Why did the spirits not choose
the strongest one?
With her as guardian,
our forest is more in danger
than ever.
Hey. Easy there, friend.
Who are you supposed to be?
Me? I am, uh, Hush's cousin.
You...
You stink like a human.
Yeah, he stepped in some human
on the way here.
Uh, Cousin Shmucas.
If he's a noise keeper,
I'm the new guardian
of the forest.
And we all know...
-..I'm not.
-Uh...oops.
Human?!
Run. Move your footsticks.
You treacherous human.
You have tricked me!
-Human?
-Oh, no, he's a human.
Don't let him get away!
Am I the only one here
who's completely confused?
Hush!
You've got a great deal
of explaining to do.
Argh!
-Huh?
-Mavka.
-Get on, quick.
The lynx will take you home.
Whoa! Sounds safe.
Nice...kitty.
Take this.
It will heal your uncle.
Thank you.
-Huh?
There's no time.
Go...and never return.
Death is the only thing
for a human to seek here.
-Go!
-Wait!
I promised I'd play for you.
Where is he? Where's the human?
He got away.
What? How did he...
You helped him?
You have the powers
of the guardian
at your disposal,
you could have -
no, you should have -
stopped him.
The guardian
doesn't need your help
deciding how and when
to use her powers, Ondina.
Mavka,
this human is no different
than all the others.
He will betray you.
And when he does,
we will all pay the price.
Hmm.
Frol!
Yes, madam?
There's something
about this boy Lucas
I don't trust.
Watch him.
I'm not so sure
he came back from the forest
empty-handed.
Me?!
Madam, I am a fashion tsar
in the making,
not a spy.
Oh, that's too bad.
If I get what I want,
I could establish you
as the number one fashion god...
..in the world.
With my own Soul of Frol
Manly Lace Boutique?
With a global chain
of whatever insane thing
you just said.
Then, if you need a spy,
why, Frol is your guy.
Ugh. Uh!
Silks, ribbons and laces
don't have to be disgraces.
That's the Soul of Frol.
No. This really happened to me.
Last night.
The forest is full of -
not demons - but creatures.
And they are
not fond of us at all.
Except Mavka. She is very nice.
Danger or no,
I have to go back to the forest
to Mavka, to thank her.
Lucas, look, if you've been at
the village fair all night long
and plan on going back,
you can just tell me.
Busted. You know me.
Party animal.
Best carnival ever.
Mmm!
So how is this,
uh, perdi-caca-something-um
supposed to work?
I have less than no idea.
-Huh?
Uncle?
Whoa!
Hah! And no pain.
I haven't stood this straight
in 20 years.
It's a miracle.
It is a miracle.
It's a miracle
of perdi-caca-something-um.
I've got so much energy.
Now I'll be Hercu-Leo.
Hey, let's take up curling.
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Yeah, it's bit more
complicated now.
But, Swampy, think for yourself.
How can he play his beautiful
music without his flute?
We have to return this to Lucas.
What if something happens
in the forest while I'm gone?
What if nothing happens
while I'm here?
You're absolutely right.
I'm the guardian now.
I can't leave the forest.
Humans are enemies.
I somehow managed to live
without Lucas before.
Or his music.
Or his eyes.
Or his smile.
Or this feeling
that now lives right here.
Hmm. Mmm.
Madam! Madam! Where's Madam?
Madam
is probably upstairs.
-Gah!
Madam! Madam!
Madam, you were right!
Eugh!
That icky boy lied to you!
Here.
Oh.
Lucas was at the Source of Life.
The heart of the forest.
And I also found this.
Finally it will be mine!
But...but there is nothing
marked here!
Now think! Did Lucas
say anything about the tree?
No!
Nothing about the tree,
but he just said
he will go into the forest again
to see the nice forest.
The magma! Boy, what a fool.
It doesn't make sense.
The nice forest magma?
Yeah, that's what he said.
He probably wants to keep
the source to himself.
-Frol.
-Yes, Madam?
-Keep an eye on this boy.
When he decides to go
to the forest,
we need to keep him company
by all means.
But on the other hand,
as the guardian,
shouldn't I learn as much
about our enemies as I can?
If Lucas isn't evil, maybe other
humans aren't evil either.
Oh, stop croaking about
the law of the forest!
Maybe it's time
for things to change
so that the forest-dwellers
and humans could live in peace.
Oh!
Uhh, no! I can't show up
looking like this.
-Hm!
Huh?
Gotta find something
a human would wear.
Hey, boy. I'm making a gift.
Yes, Dot,
Mavka is going to love me.
Uh, it! It.
And...done.
-Hey, where are the pies?!
Pie-demolisher!
-It's fine.
I'm not perfect either.
For instance, I'm about to
break my promise to Hush
and the forest law
in order to keep
my promise to Mavka.
Mavka, are you here?
Your hair! How are you here?
Aren't you happy to see me?
No. I mean, yes!
Heart-burstingly happy,
which is a thing I probably
shouldn't say out loud.
Oh, is this your nest?
I prefer
to think of it as a cave.
Is this for making music too?
-Uh, no.
Those are regular instruments,
not musical instruments.
I've come to return your flute.
It was broken, but I...
Here.
Thank you.
Now you can go to the stone
forest and follow your dream.
Just play for me one last time
and then I'll leave.
No. No, don't leave!
Uh, I have an idea.
I'll play even better music
for you.
There's a festival in town and
my band is playing. Let's go!
-Uh...
- Don't be afraid.
It'll be good
for guardian of the forest
to know more about us humans,
right?
Uh...
-You're gonna love it.
Huh?
Mavka, let's find you
an outfit that says,
"I am a non-alarming
local human."
What's wrong with this one?
Well, it kind of screams,
"Howdy, I'm a barely disguised
forest demon
"from behind the Dark Mountain."
Oh!
Oh.
-Oh!
-Hm?
-And this is my uncle Leo.
-Oh!
He's the one you saved
with your gift.
Hm?
What have you done?
Oh! Those are
my friends playing.
This music, the dancing -
how delightful!
But you still play better
than anybody else.
He was born that way!
So, Lucas,
Uncle Leo is recovered.
He looks better than you now.
Isn't it time to show
your talent to the big city?
Um, well...
Or has the music shown you
a different way?
A very beautiful way.
Well, your call, Romeo.
We're always happy
to have you with us.
Pack up. We gotta go.
Oh, that's right, it's late.
I must go too.
Thank you for the wonderful time
and for the gift.
Wait! I haven't fulfilled
my promise yet.
-Look! A demon from the forest!
-She's glowing!
-Green hair!
An evil spirit from behind
the Dark Mountain!
What shall we do?
She's come to kill
our lovey ones
and destroy our food crops!
No! It's not true!
This lad is trying
to protect the demon.
She has bewitched him.
-She'll put a curse on us.
Get her!
No! She won't hurt anyone.
-Lucas!
No!
- Hm...
-Argh!
Let me go! Lucas!
What do we do?
-Burn her, right?
-No, they drown witches!
Let's do both!
My fellow villagers,
I was wrong.
The evil spirits of the forest
are very real.
And now I see that it was her
kind that burned up my father,
the goodly sawmill owner.
How dare she!
But fear not!
My eyes are open now
and I will find out what
the demons have in store for us,
be it plague...
-..drought...
-..famine, fire or flood!
And where the Source of Life is.
-Oh!
-What is this?!
-What's happening?
-Black magic!
-Argh!
Don't let her get away!
-Lesh!
Where'd he go?
Is he gone?
All is lost!
My strong silks, my robust
ribbons, my manly laces,
the Soul of Frol - gone!
Oh!
It isn't over yet,
my whiny little pet.
My poor, dear,
terrified fellow villagers,
we underestimated
the demon's power
and the results were tragic.
But this is not the end.
They'll soon be back!
-Oh, no! What do we do?
-Oh, this is terrible!
There's only one way
to stop this evil.
Strike first!
Lesh,
how did you find me?
Hush told me everything.
I don't understand what's
happening. Those humans...
Calm down now.
Those humans obviously conspired
to lure you into a trap.
I love how no matter where you
look, you see goodness, Mavka,
but you have made
the same mistake I made once
in trusting a human.
Lucas would never do that.
I'm sure
he can explain everything.
-Mavka!?
Now, Lucas,
be a good boy of limited
intellect and integrity
and mark the Source of Life
on this crudely drawn map.
Never gonna happen, lady.
Somebody found a backbone!
Let's see if we can't just
melt it like meringue.
Ooh, I'm peckish.
Oh, no!
Don't touch her!
The source...
-..or she dies.
Now let Mavka go!
Sure thing, ding-a-ling.
Oh, Lucas!
Smooch, smooch, swoon!
Oh, you saved me! You saved me!
You're so, so dumb.
No! Kylina, you won't
get away with this!
-Ah! Ah!
Really?
Guess I'll just stop, then.
Have a nice swim, sweetie!
So much water has flowed past
since that fateful day,
the time has come for me
to tell the full truth.
The battle
all those winters ago -
I've never told anyone
the reason why it happened.
The sawmill owner
came to me in tears.
He was begging me to save
his newborn daughter...
..and I believed in goodness
in him.
I gave this human
a drop from
the Source of Life itself.
Soon, he returned with...
..well, with an army of humans.
They wanted the Source of Life
for themselves.
So, I called for the Supreme
Spirit of the Underworld,
the One Who Sits in the Rock,
to give me the Spark of Rage.
And, may all those I love
forgive me,
he did.
Everything good in me
was replaced by sheer rage.
I burned and the world burned.
Humans and the forest alike.
Fire and hatred without end.
Have you seen Lucas?
Have you seen my boy, Lucas?
Oh!
Your boy's been taken by
the evil forest demons.
-Huh?
-Stings, right?
But you can still save him
if you join us.
Take the weapon, old man.
I'm on a schedule here!
You stay here and make sure
nobody finds the boy...
..unless you were just dying
to be in the battle?
This is for our home!
And my youthful skin.
Now let's go
eradicate those demons
for the good of
all we hold dear!
-Yes!
-Yes! Death to the demons!
Start the forest killer!
Humans are preparing
to attack the forest.
Uh!
Hey! Somebody! Anybody! Hey!
Dot? Dot, is that you?
Good boy!
Run! Find someone to help me!
Hurry!
So, that's it. War is here.
The sawmill owner's daughter...
I know what to do!
What? Decorate their axes
with flowers?
I know what we all need to do -
fight!
No! There's another way!
I am the guardian
and this is my call. Wait here.
-Don't look at me.
She is the guardian.
What's going on?
Whoa!
Please stop!
Hm.
I might've frightened
the people at the fair,
but the forest means no harm
to humans.
We can live in peace
and even help each other.
"Help each other"?
A long time ago,
the forest gave a drop
from the Source of Life
to the owner of the sawmill
so he could heal
his sick newborn daughter.
The forest saved you!
What? Nobody ever told me!
It is the truth.
The truth?
The truth is the sawmill owner
never had a daughter,
but he had a beautiful wife that
came up with a tragic story
about a little sick daughter.
My husband was obedient
but weak.
He only got me
the one lousy drop
that kept me young and fit
for all these years.
But how does this
make us enemies?
Oh, you'll never
understand this. Look at you!
You're Nature's queen,
glowing and gorgeous forever!
You don't know nothing about
crow's-feet, turkey neck,
back fat.
You'll never get old
and saggy and shrivelled.
But I can give you
one more drop.
That is so nice of you,
but, see, if I get hold of
the entire Source of Life,
I will not only be young
and beautiful forever,
but it'll also make me
the richest,
most powerful woman ever.
But without the Source of Life,
the forest will die.
It's gonna die
one way or the other, honey,
so why not just
get out of my way?
Hm.
Not all humans are
as cruel and selfish as you are!
Oh, you're thinking about
that lad of yours? Lucas?
Huh?
Do you have any idea
where he is?
I...
I'll tell you another truth,
sister.
I paid Lucas very well
so he would find the source
and lure you into the village.
-Huh?
-He took his money and left.
To the city?
Exactly.
Oh.
And one more thing.
Lucas told me it was
almost too easy to fool you
because you're just so nice.
Oh.
Now get out of my way
and take your
freaky woodland zoo with you!
Mavka! I knew we couldn't
trust that Shmucas!
I got it so wrong, Hush.
Humans really are all evil.
Lucas is...
Huh! Huh!
Who are you, friend?
You're saying
Shmucas didn't betray us?!
-Do you believe him?
Then I have an idea.
Mm! Frol Style!
Madam is going to love it!
Huh?
Well? Where's our hero?
Hm! Hm!
Go get Shmucas
and I'll deal with this one.
-Huh?
Hm!
Argh!
I will slice you into
robust little ribbons!
Dot?
Get back here,
you rotten cabbage!
Oh-ho-ho! You have
awakened the beast now!
Knock, knock! Anybody home?
Ooh!
-Hm.
Am I glad to see you!
Ooh!
Oh-oh-oh!
Huh? Oh!
Hm.
So, that's where you're hiding,
you rotten old stump!
This is all my fault.
I have to stop this.
Supreme Spirit,
the One Who Sits in the Rock,
I call on you!
No! Mavka, don't!
You have called me, Guardian.
I beg you, give me the strength
to answer my calling.
I need the Spark of Rage
to protect the forest.
The Spark of Rage has its price.
The price paid
by the previous guardian
was his enormous strength.
The rage burned him out
from the inside.
And you,
the Spark will cost you
your life.
You shall enter the Nothingness
for eternity.
I agree, for this
treacherous feeling here,
now it brings only pain.
As you wish, Guardian.
Ondina was right.
I was too nice.
Whoa!
I forgot to mention...
I've got you now, weed-face!
..I'm allergic to chainsaws!
Hush, you alright?
Oh, Shmucas!
I'm fine. Got some yellow spots,
but, overall, fine.
-Huh?
This village has the worst aura!
Hush, please,
I need to find Mavka!
What the hometown hurricane
is that?!
It seems that IS Mavka.
Oh!
-Whoa!
Mavka!
It's me, Lucas! I'm here!
Argh, I've got to get closer!
I might be able to help
with that.
Thank you, dear cousin.
Ha! They'll call me Hush,
who first befriended humans.
Uh...uh... Whoa!
-Whoa!
Mavka! It's me!
Please! You have to stop!
Aah!
Whoa! Aah! Oh!
-Oh!
Where are you going?
You're gonna die!
I don't care.
I have to save her.
There's nothing you can do.
She can no longer understand
your words. Do you copy?
What did you say?
I said she can't hear
your words! Run!
Hush, you are a genius!
Finally I can scratch
hearing that off my bucket list!
She can't hear my words,
but what if...
I got it! I got it!
They need our help.
We should all do this together!
Mavka, it's me.
Hear me, please!
Come back to me. Please!
Is this what Nothingness
feels like?
This is
the place of no phantom dreams,
where no songs are carried
by the wind.
The fire of hate and rage
does not burn here.
Rage doesn't burn
in my heart anymore.
I heard his voice and now
I know he never betrayed me.
You have chosen
to spare the lives of the humans
who have caused you
so much pain.
But they also
gave me something
I've never felt before.
We have made the right choice
making you the new guardian.
You have bridged the gap
between the humans
and the forest-dwellers,
but now you have to pay
the promised price
and remain in
the Nothingness forever.
For eternity.
No.
I'm alive
and I will live on forever
because now my heart is full of
something that will never die.
Through the darkness,
I heard your music.
It filled me here.
Your music is the real magic.
No.
The only magic humans have
is love.
Uh?
♪ Sing me
your woodland ballad... ♪
I think it's time
to end our feud.
Peace?
♪ And let there be
endless pride... ♪
♪ Let the star
rise and shine... ♪
Peace, friend.
♪ Be on my side
♪ Fly as the wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ That keeps our souls alive
♪ So, let the dawn fires
♪ Keep burning
♪ Warming and lighting
♪ Our hearts
♪ And olden times
♪ Sacred knowing
♪ Lead us the way to a new start
♪ And olden times
♪ Sacred knowing
♪ Lead us the way to a new start
♪ Faith and fate now
♪ Be on my side
♪ Fly as a wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ Fly as a wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ Let there be endless pride
♪ Let the star rise and shine
♪ Faith and fate now
♪ Be on my side
♪ Fly as a wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ That keeps our souls alive. ♪
I've found it!
I've finally found it!
It's finally mine!
Yes!
Mmm!
Take that, ravages of time!
Fresh and firm forev...
Huh? What? No! No! No!