(MUSIC BOX
PLAYING GENTLE MELODY)
-(SIREN BLARING)
-(MUSIC BOX STOPS)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
-(BELL JINGLING)
-(GODLOCK PANTING)
(BELL JINGLING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
(TRAIN HORN BLOWS)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(TRAIN WHEELS SQUEALING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BACKGROUND CHATTER)
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(DISTANT GUNSHOTS)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(GUNFIRE)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(GUN FIRING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR ENGINES SPEEDING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT LAUGHTER)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS, PANTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
-(TRAIN HORN BLARING)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GUNS FIRING)
(MAN GROANS)
(GROANING)
(CAR HONKING HORN)
-(MAN GROANS)
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LOUD CRASHING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
-(HONKING CONTINUES)
-(GODLOCK PANTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTING)
-(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
-(MEN YELPING)
(CAR CRASHING)
-(GUNS FIRING)
-(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTING, PANTING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(FORKLIFT BEEPING)
(GUN FIRING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(MAN YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GODLOCK GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BLOOD SQUELCHING)
(GODLOCK GURGLES, CHOKES)
MALE SINGER:
♪ Silent night
♪ Holy night
(SAYA PANTING)
♪ All is calm
♪ All is bright
♪ Round yon
Virgin Mother and Child
♪ Holy infant
♪ So tender and mild
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace
(SAYA CRIES, WHIMPERS)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
CHOIR: (SINGING)
♪ Silent night
(DOCTOR AND NURSE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
♪ Holy night
♪ Shepherds quake
♪ At the sight
♪ Glories stream
(SAYA WHIMPERS)
♪ From afar ♪
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
DOCTOR: Suction.
(SUCTION MACHINE HISSING)
♪ Heavenly hosts
sing Alleluia ♪
(BUBBLING)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
♪ Christ the Savior is born!
(SAYA SOBBING)
♪ Christ the Savior
♪ Is born ♪
(DOOR CLOSES)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING,
VENTILATOR HISSING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRD CHIRPS)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(GODLOCK COUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
Okay.
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING VOICELESSLY)
(CROAKS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELECTRONIC VOICE)
(ELECTROLARYNX
CLATTERS ON FLOOR)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
MAN: (OVER RADIO)
It's Wednesday, January 26th,
and you're listening
to 88.3 KPLP.
In just a few hours,
the Federal Reserve is
projected to raise
interest rates,
and we're told
that this is their main tool
to help lower inflation.
Can you just explain to us...
-(CHILDREN CHATTER EXCITEDLY)
-WOMAN: (OVER RADIO)
Sure, sure.
So, as everyone knows,
the prices are rising...
(CHILDREN CHATTERING, SHOUTING)
(RADIO HOSTS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
WOMAN: Exactly.
And the spending...
(WOMAN CONTINUES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
The labor markets...
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(CAR ENGINE IDLING)
WOMAN: (OVER RADIO)
...higher rate,
which obviously
the government does not want.
So, what the Fed
is saying is that
if they raise
these interest rates,
if they make these commodities
such as cars and houses
actually more expensive,
then fewer people will be able
to afford them.
This will lower the demand
and give the supply the chance
to catch up...
MAN: Right.
-So, tell us the story...
-(CHAIN CLANKS)
...of how we got here.
When did all this start?
WOMAN: So, our story starts...
(PARKING BRAKES ENGAGE)
(KISSES)
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
-(SIREN WAILS)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(TAYLOR GIGGLES)
(GODLOCK CHUCKLES)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
-(TAYLOR GIGGLES)
(GIGGLING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CROW SQUAWKING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
-(WALKING STICK CLANKING)
-(CLOCK TICKING)
(MOURNFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GODLOCK THUDS ON FLOOR)
(SOBBING SILENTLY)
(SOBS)
SAYA: Hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
(WEEPING COPIOUSLY)
(CLOCK DINGING)
(GROWLS ANGRILY)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Stop it...
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(FRIDGE DOOR CLOSES)
(GODLOCK CHOKES)
(GASPS)
(MOUTHING) Help me.
(CRYING) How?
(SNIFFLES)
(RAVEN CAWING)
WOMAN: (OVER RADIO)
It's Thursday, April 14th,
KPLP's Lifestyle Fridays,
Holiday Weekend Edition.
Coming up,
how to make the most...
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
...of your long
Easter weekend
and fun Easter egg ideas
that your kids will love.
-All that...
-(RADIO TURNS OFF)
(BAG RUSTLING)
(GLASS CLINKS)
(GODLOCK GULPS)
(GLASS THUDS)
(POURING DRINK)
(CELLPHONE KEYPAD CLACKING)
(NOTIFICATION DINGS)
(KEYPAD CLACKING)
(GLASS CLINKS)
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(GLASS THUDS)
-(DOOR OPENS)
-(CHAIR SQUEAKING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MUSIC BOX
PLAYING GENTLE MELODY)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC BOX MELODY ECHOING)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(SOBBING)
(GODLOCK WHIMPERS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SOBS)
(TRAIN HORN
BLARING IN DISTANCE)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S CHRISTMAS PLAYING)
♪ I can't believe
That it's Christmas
♪ The best time of the year
♪ Whoa
♪ I can't believe
That it's Christmas
♪ And Santa will soon be here
♪ It's such a warm
And jolly feeling
♪ And Santa is someone
We all believe in
(TAYLOR GIGGLING)
♪ He's in a hurry
But don't you worry
♪ Your stocking
Won't be empty
♪ You'll see
♪ I can't believe
That it's Christmas
♪ The best time of the year
♪ Whoa
♪ I can't believe...
-(GODLOCK CHUCKLES)
-SAYA: Hey.
You wanna fly?
♪ Santa's working
Around the clock
♪ Rudolph's running around
every block... ♪
(CAR TIRES SCREECHING)
-(BRAKES SCREECHING)
-(GUNFIRE)
SAYA: (SHRIEKS) No! No!
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
SAYA: No! No! No! No!
(SAYA CRYING)
(BELL JINGLING)
GODLOCK: No!
(SAYA SHUDDERING)
(SOBBING)
(GODLOCK SCREAMS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
(OBJECTS RUSTLING)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(SAYA EXHALES)
(POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(BLOWS AIR GENTLY)
-(BIRDS CHIRPING)
-(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(NOTIFICATION CHIMES)
-(BOTTLE CLATTERING)
-(NOTIFICATION DINGS)
(NOTIFICATION DINGS)
(CELLPHONE VIBRATES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Hey.
(PHONE RINGING IN DISTANCE)
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
(PHONE CAMERA CLICKS)
(PHONE CAMERA CLICKING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(PHONE CAMERA CLICKING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLICKING)
(SQUEAKING, CLANKING)
(HANDLE BAR CREAKS)
(GRUNTS)
-(CLICKING)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTING)
TRAINER: (OVER PHONE)
...across the inside
of the forearm
stops the attacker
from grabbing you.
Otherwise his extremities
will be able to block...
I can get inside his defense
and limit his ability.
Cut here.
Now I'm getting
positive stab and cut.
Now remember, make sure
that you twist the blade,
torquing your blade
to the left...
Now I cut directly across...
inside and around.
So I stab upwards,
causing pressure...
Now, driving my blade out
creates a large, gaping wound.
(TRAINER CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(PENDULUM CLICKING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(ROUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIREN BLARES)
(ENGINE STARTS, REVS)
(WINDSHIELD WIPER WHIRRING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE REVS)
(TOOL CRACKLING)
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SAYA EXHALES)
(DRILLING CONTINUES)
(SAYA SNIFFLES)
(BULLET CLANGS)
(GUN COCKS)
(SHELL CASING CLATTERING)
(GUN CLICKS)
(TOOL CRACKLING)
(DISTANT HAMMERING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
OFFICER 1: (OVER RADIO)
Shots fired. Shots fired.
3500 North 13th.
Shots fired on the corner
of 13th and Paul.
We have shots fired.
OFFICER 2: (OVER RADIO)
Copy, 4-0.
All units,
all units North 13th.
Officer-involved shooting.
Respond with caution.
OFFICER 1: (OVER RADIO)
39th District.
3500 North 13th,
still shots fired.
Third call. 3500 North 13th.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(SAYA SOBS)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(ENGINE ROARING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(CLICKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(TECHNO MUSIC
PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT CHEERING)
(HORN BLOWING)
(TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(CAMERA BEEPING)
(CAMERA LENS WHIRRING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(CAMERA ZOOMING IN)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
(PENDULUM CLICKING)
(SLOW DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(SHELL CASING CLATTERING)
(TARGET WHIRRING)
(CLICKING)
(WE WISH YOU A MERRY CHRISTMAS
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
♪ We wish you
A merry Christmas
♪ And a happy new year ♪
(WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GODLOCK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GODLOCK GASPS)
(CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYING)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHILDREN
CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNIFE SLASHES)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
(GODLOCK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(LAUGHTER ECHOING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(CACKLES)
(CAR HONKS)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(LOUD HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER CAR STEREO)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNIFE SLICING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DOG BARKING DISTANTLY)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(SOFT THUD)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(MUFFLED CRIES)
(GODLOCK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUDS)
(MAN GROANS)
(GASPING)
(MAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MUFFLED) Fuck you!
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(MAN YELPS)
(MAN PANTING)
(CLOCK CHIMES)
(METAL HELMET CLANKS)
-(KNIFE SLICES)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(GODLOCK WINCING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(METAL CLANKING)
(MAN GROANS)
(MAN YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(MAN YELLING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(KNIFE CLATTERS)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(GODLOCK PANTING)
(WOOD CREAKS)
(TABLE CREAKING, THUDS)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GUN COCKS)
(PEN SCRIBBLING)
(PEN THUDS)
(MUSIC BOX
PLAYING GENTLE MELODY)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(WRAPPING PAPER RUSTLING)
(THUDDING ON DOOR)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DOG BARKING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(SIREN BLARING)
(DISPATCHER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
Reports of a possible
211 outside Bar Martins.
OFFICER 1: (OVER RADIO)
5-3-0,
currently on Belview Park,
headed into south.
DISPATCHER: Copy, 530.
1500 block of Allen
in the alleyway
-behind Bar Martins.
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
(UPBEAT CHRISTMAS
CAROL PLAYING)
(POLICE DISPATCHER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
-No! No! No!
-(MAN GRUNTS)
WOMAN: (SHRIEKS) No! No! No!
No! No!
No! No! No! No!
-(MAN WHIMPERS)
-WOMAN: No! No!
-(MAN GRUNTING)
-WOMAN: No! No! No!
No!
No! No!
(DISPATCHER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
(WOMAN CRYING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GOONS LAUGHING)
(WOMAN CRYING)
(SOBBING)
(GOONS LAUGHING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(ROBBER YELLS)
-(SCREAMING)
-(BONES CRUSHING)
-(KNIFE STABS)
-(ROBBER GURGLES)
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ROBBER SCREAMING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
-(ROBBER SCREAMING)
-(ENGINE REVVING)
-(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUN SHOTS FIRING)
(CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYS)
(BLOOD SQUELCHING)
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
(GODLOCK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RETCHING)
(BLOOD ON THE BLADE
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ God's telling me
Fuck your friends
♪ Fuck your enemies
-(CAR DOOR OPENS)
-(ENGINE WHIRRING)
♪ So I look at the sky
♪ 'Cause its color is blue
♪ 'Cause I'm fucked
If I don't
♪ And I'm fucked if I do
♪ Tears on the altar
♪ Blood on the blade
♪ There's blood on my blade
♪ Tears on the altar
♪ Blood on my blade
♪ There's blood on my blade
♪ There's blood on my blade!
(MAN SNIFFING)
♪ To pave your way
♪ Blame the preachers
You burned
♪ Lightin' the way
♪ Tears on the altar
♪ Blood on the blade
♪ Blood on the blade ♪
(GUNS FIRING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN SCREAMS)
-(GUNFIRE)
-(GANG MEMBER 1 GROANS)
OFFICER 1: (OVER RADIO)
6-0-4, I think
it's a gang war.
-I...I need backup.
-(SIRENS WAILING).
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
Copy that. Any available
units, please confirm.
(GANG MEMBER 2 GROANS)
OFFICER 2: (OVER RADIO)
81st Street.
Shots fired from inside.
OFFICER 3: (OVER RADIO)
It's a war zone out here.
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
All units. All units.
Multiple reports of gang war.
OFFICER 4: (OVER RADIO)
Jesus Christ.
Merry fucking Christmas.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CONVERSATION)
(GANG MEMBER 3 SHOUTING)
(GANG MEMBER 4 GROANS)
(OFFICER 1 SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
(OFFICER 5 WHIMPERS, SHRIEKS)
OFFICER 2: (OVER RADIO)
2-0-5, we...
we have gangbangers.
We have gangbangers...
-(GUNS FIRING)
-(ENGINE REVVING)
OFFICER 1: Dispatch, dispatch,
this is 6-0-4. I got a...
-(GUN FIRES)
-(GANG MEMBER 5 GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GANG MEMBER 6 GROANS)
-(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
-(GUNS FIRING ON VIDEO)
-(GUNSHOT)
-(GANG MEMBER GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
(OFFICER 5 SHRIEKS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(DISPATCHER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
Automatic weapons,
automatic weapons.
I repeat. All units,
all units, please respond.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
Reports of automatic weapons.
OFFICER 1:
This is 6-0-4,
I'm taking fire.
(GANG MEMBER SHOUTING)
OFFICER 1:
I need backup. ASAP!
OFFICER 2: (OVER RADIO)
2-0-5. We need medical now!
We need medical.
OFFICER 3: Dispatch, 3-0-2,
we're getting out of here.
There's too many packin'.
DISPATCHER:
All units, stand down.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(GANG MEMBERS
YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(GROANING)
-(GANG MEMBER WINCING)
-(CELLPHONE SHATTERS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(GANG MEMBERS
SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GANG MEMBER GROANS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
-(MAN GROANS)
-(CELLPHONE RINGING)
(GANG MEMBER WHISTLES)
(MAN PANTING)
-(RUIZ GRUNTS)
-(BLOOD SQUELCHES)
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(SIGHS)
(ENGINE IDLING)
(COMPARTMENT OPENS)
(WINDING KEY)
-(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
-(SIRENS WAILING DISTANTLY)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC BOX STOPS PLAYING)
(ENGINE REVS)
-(CRASHING)
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(HORN BLARING)
(YELLING) Move! Move! Move!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(HORN BLARING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORN BLARING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
-(ENGINE REVS)
-(TIRES SCREECH)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(BULLETS CLANKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
-(CRASHING)
-(GLASS SHATTERING)
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING)
(GUN FIRING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BODY THUDS)
-(PANTING)
-(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(SIREN BLARING)
(RUIZ GROANING)
(CHOKING, COUGHING)
OFFICER 1: (OVER RADIO)
6-0-4,
still taking fire.
Still shooting.
OFFICER 2:
All units, stand down.
All units, all personnel,
stand by for new orders.
OFFICER 3: Merry Christmas.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
OFFICER 2: (OVER RADIO)
Unit 76-15, please contact.
OFFICER 4: 513,
still need medical
at 700 Third.
Both sides still firing.
OFFICER 2:
Mike, Bravo, 5-19 en route.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
OFFICER 5: (OVER RADIO)
Mike, Bravo, 5-19...
OFFICER 2: If your gun
is required, pull it out.
All units, all personnel,
be advised.
The order
to remain outside
the perimeter
is still in force.
(KEYS JINGLING)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
OFFICER 2: (OVER RADIO)
All units, pull back.
All units,
stand by for new orders.
(ENGINE REVS)
(PARALYZER BY SUUNS
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ I just wanna touch you
♪ And hold you
In my hands
♪ I just wanna touch you
♪ And feel you
With my hands
♪ Give everyone a chance
♪ Give everyone a chance ♪
(WOMAN WHIMPERS)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(WINDING KEY)
(MUSIC BOX
PLAYING MELODY)
(GUN COCKS)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(MELODY CONTINUES PLAYING)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING)
(GATE ALARM BLARES)
(CRASHES)
(GUNS FIRING)
(GANG MEMBER 1 GRUNTS)
(GANG MEMBER 2 GRUNTS)
(GANG MEMBERS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GODLOCK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GANG MEMBERS
SHOUTING, CHATTERING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(GANG MEMBER 1 GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT FIRES)
(GANG MEMBER 2
MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY)
(GANG MEMBER 3 GRUNTS)
(GANG MEMBER 2 YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GANG MEMBER 2 GROANS)
(GANG MEMBER 4 GROANS)
(GANG MEMBER 5
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
-(GRUNTS)
-(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(KNIFE THWACKS)
-(GANG MEMBER 6 SCREAMING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GANG MEMBERS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
GANG MEMBER 7:
You motherfucker! You...
-(GUNSHOT FIRES)
-(GANG MEMBER 7 GROANS)
(GODLOCK GRUNTING)
-GANG MEMBER 7: You fucker!
-(SHOTS FIRING)
(GANG MEMBER 7 GROANS)
(GUN CLICKS)
(GANG MEMBER 8 GRUNTING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTING)
(GANG MEMBER 8 YELLS)
(SCREAMS)
(METAL CLANKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GUN COCKS)
(SHOTS FIRING)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(GANG MEMBERS GROANING)
(GODLOCK PANTING)
(EXHALES)
(WIRE CLANKING)
(RUIZ GRUNTS)
(GODLOCK GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(RUIZ GRUNTS)
(GODLOCK GROANS)
(GROANING)
-(RUIZ GRUNTS)
-(GODLOCK GROANS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GODLOCK GRUNTS)
(RUIZ GROANS)
-(KNIFE STABS)
-(RUIZ SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GODLOCK PANTING)
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
(GUN FIRING DISTANTLY)
(RUIZ GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHOTS FIRING)
(GUN COCKS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(YELLS)
(CARTRIDGE CLANKS)
(YELLING)
(GODLOCK GROANS)
(SUBMACHINE GUN FIRING)
(FIRING CONTINUES)
(GUN CLICKING)
(GUN COCKS)
(GUN CLATTERS ON FLOOR)
(VENUS BREATHING HEAVILY)
(VENUS GASPS)
(GODLOCK GROANS)
-(GROANS)
-(SCOFFS)
(VASSEL GROANS)
(VENUS GROANS)
(BODY THUDS)
(GODLOCK GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DARKSEID BY GRIMES
& PAN PLAYING)
♪ Unrest is in the soul
♪ We don't move
Our bodies anymore
♪ Unrest is in the soul
♪ We don't move
Our bodies anymore ♪
(GODLOCK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GUNSHOT)
(VASSELL SPITS)
(PLAYA GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(PLAYA CHOKING)
(CHOKING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(MUSIC BOX
MELODY ECHOING)
(GODLOCK THUDS ON FLOOR)
(VASSELL GROANING)
(MUSIC BOX
MELODY PLAYING)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BABY TAYLOR CRYING)
(TAYLOR GIGGLES)
(STUDENTS APPLAUDING)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOLEMN MUSIC FADES OUT)
(INSTRUMENTAL
SILENT NIGHT PLAYING)
(SILENT NIGHT
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING)