Hey, there.
Sorry to bother you, folks,
but, uh, we're looking
for an individual.
Golden-brown complexion.
15 pounds.
No head.
I know where he is.
I'll even serve him up
on a silver platter for you.
Now get in here.
I'm glad to see you finally
out of your man cave.
Well, you know, Amanda
can be pretty convincing
when she wants to be.Hey, babe. Eric's here.
Hey, Amanda.
Well, well, well, well.
You made it.Yeah.
Sorry.
Thomas. One second.
I baked this for you.
I couldn't eat it by myself.
It would just be too depressing.
Wow.
You baked this?
Yeah, you know,
for a single guy,
I know my way around the oven.
Ah... A guy in uniform
who knows how to bake.
I have a feeling you're not
gonna be single for long.
Come on. You remember my mom,
right?
Hey, Mom, remember Eric?WOMAN: Oh, hey.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Uh, do you want any or...?: No, no.
Jeans and a sweater?
You could at least
make an effort.
Casual's more my thing,
Kathleen.
Especially in my own house.
Don't you mean "our house" now?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.JESSICA: Hi, Dad.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Oh, thank God you're back,
Thomas.
Thought we'd be eating
a frozen turkey dinner.
This guy.
Sorry, Rob.
Yeah, this is the first time
the store's open
on Thanksgiving.
You know, we always do the,
uh, midnight Black Friday,
but people were showing up
at 6:00 p.m. anyway, so...
And you're a smart man, Thomas.
Yeah, well, credit my beautiful
fiancée over there.
It was her idea.
Well, from what
I've been hearing
about the turnout,
it is going to be
a very happy Thanksgiving.
Here we go.
Oh, that's beautiful. Yes.
Mitch, we need
your carving skills.
I've got time to carve it
but not to eat it.
Oh, what?Thomas is not making you work.
Blame Bob.
Apparently, he's AWOL.
Thomas called and said
it's me working or I'm fired.
Oh, sorry,buddy.
Aw! The store shouldn't
even be open.
It's Thanksgiving.
I know, Mary,
but let's face it.
Black Friday starts
on a Thursday now.
Even in Plymouth.
Hey, Bon Jovi,
why don't you get to the back
of the fucking line, okay?Yeah, suck my dick!
We were here first.
Hey, everybody.
Just fucking calm down.
Two hits. I hit you,
you hit the ground, kid!
What the fuck?!
Jesus, everybody, be patient!LONNIE: Hey, fuck you!
Let us in, or you'll be
a patient in Mass General.
What the fuck is wrong
with you people?
Fucking funny, eh?
The store opens in ten minutes.
You'll get your waffle iron!
Xanax?No, you got a fire hose?
Todd,
I need you at the register.
Thank you.
Bunch of goddamn morons.
When Kathleen sold my dad
this house,
I didn't realize
she was coming with it.
She'll never be able
to replace your mom, Jess.
Yeah.
And look at it this way.
It was a quick engagement,
so hopefully it'll be
a quick divorce.
Please, God.
Oh. Let's go.
Dad, we're going to the movies.Have fun. Uh, Bobby,
I want to hear about
that 19-strikeout game
against UCLA, when you get back.
Deal, Thomas.
Good night, everyone.
Scuba invited Yulia.
He's into her.
Got it. I'll gas him up.
Okay.
Bobby.
Bobby Boucher.
Bobby "Golden Arm"
home for Thanksgiving,
and my ride or die, J-Money.What up, dawg?
I heard you're
the new Friday Night guy.
Ah, I'd better be, with
a 96-mile-per-hour fastball.
Evan, you are such a dick.What?
Yo, nice job beating Hanover.
Scuba, I heard
you were unstoppable.
Thanks, man.
It was a pretty good night
until Tyson Fury over here
almost got us
locked the fuck up.
Classic Evan.JESSICA: Why? What happened?
We got in a run-in with
some drunk Hanover assholes.
Fuck Hanover.I popped one of them
in the eye,
but this one was too busy
filming herself
to get some fucking footage.
Shit would've
broke the Internets.
You are lucky
I didn't film that, okay?
It was, like,
Waffle House-level cringe.
It was bad.
♪ Crunk ain't dead, crunk ain't
dead, crunk ain't dead... ♪
Fuck Hanover!
Fuck Hanover! Fuck Hanover!
This fucking traffic
is ridiculous.
Oh, I can't handle
this shit.
Yo.
Pit stop. I need a new phone.
Mine got fucking smashed
in the fight.
We're not going to the store.
It's a zoo.
Whoa, no, no, no, yes, we are,
'cause Evan owes me
a new lipstick.
Thank you.Don't worry, don't worry...
What?BOBBY: Guys, I thought
we were going to the movies.Yeah, we-we are.
We are. How am I gonna text
during the movie
without a phone?
Who are you texting?
♪ Oh... shit! ♪
♪ Oh, shit! ♪
Hey! Wrong way, asshole!
Hey!
♪ Oh, shit! ♪
Guys, we need to do
this quick, okay?
Five minutes. In and out.YULIA: Go, go.
Stealth mission, I promise.
You can't park your car here.
It's not a car, it's an SUV.
Hey, babe, c-can I just
stay here, please?
Please don't make me
do this alone.
I...
Bobby, can I get a selfie?
Hey, one-one second.
I'll be right back.
Hey, man. What's up?Yo.
Bobby, Bobby,
we have to move.
Yeah, yeah,
one second, one second.
Bobby "Golden Arm,"
all-time record holder
for strikeouts at Plymouth East!Yes, sir.
Hey, Jess.Hey.
This is, like, the last place
I thought I'd see you tonight.
Yeah, you and me both.
Your dad's store
is insane right now.
Look at all these people.
Um, sorry, Ryan, I-I have to
catch up with my friends.Oh, I'll walk you.
Come on. Come on.
So, uh, what are you doing
Saturday night?
Going to the Cap with Bobby.
All right, well...
Uh, excuse me...
I'm having a little
get-together with my friends...
Excuse me... and, uh, you know,
if you wanted to come by,
it's just gonna be like
a couple people...
I can't. Bobby's only in town
till Monday, so...
You should just swing by early.
We could, like,
play some drinking games,
have a good time, you know.
I got some kegs.
She's all set, Ryan.
Come on. Let's go.
Excuse me.
Chill out,
he's just helping.
Oh, what a gentleman.
Face it.
As long as Golden Arm's around,
you're toast.
Scott. Scott.Burnt. Toast.
Shut the fuck up, Scott.Burnt soggy toast.
I love you, dude,
but I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Mm, try your best.
Want to open that gate
for us, gentlemen?
Excuse me, excuse me.Here, Amanda, get in here.
Oh, my God.
Good evening.Good evening, Sheriff.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck you.
This is insane.
Yeah. Let's go in the back.Okay.
Hey!
Hey, you! We got some
unfinished business, you fuck!
Oh, fuck, that's the guy
from Hanover I punched.
Fuck you!
Suck my cock!
Pussy.
Hey, fuck you!
Fuck your mom, fucking pussies!
Yo, Lonnie,
where's your mom at? -Hey!
That's what I thought!Fuck your cousin,
your second cousin
and fuck your dog!
Let's just get what you need
and get out of here.
In and out, I promise.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Why are you fucking letting
those fucking jerkoffs in there?
Hello? I fucking see you.
It's Thanks-fucking-giving!
It's an American holiday!
Come on, man.
It's a pizza oven.
Where do you think it goes?MAN: Sorry, Mitch.
Ten minutes, people.
Please, come on.
Hi. Surprise.Hey.
Hey, babe.
What are you doing here?
I came in with Eric.
I didn't want you to starve
on Thanksgiving.Yeah.
I got a call on the radio
about needing some
crowd control.
Uh, yeah.
In fact, you should
probably wait in here, okay?
Okay. Are you okay?
Yeah. We should...Yeah?
We should go.Be careful.
Fucking guy Lonnie's
30 years old.
Dude, he's just madHe got held back
I took his mom to prom.Two years
and she gave me a handy.And he's dating a cheerleader.
Hey, Jess, does your dad
still sell shock collars?
Or a tranquilizer?Or a sedative?
This is like in the fucking
apocalypse movies...
Evan....where you could
take anything you want.
Evan!
Scuba.JESSICA: Come on.
You know what time it is,
boys.
Guys.
Let's go. Fletcher...
Oh, my God, here we go.
to Dybing!
What happened
to stealth mission?
Come on.
The store will open
in ten minutes.
Fucking Christ!Just stay calm, take a breath.
Everybody's gonna get
their Furbies, all right?
Oh, yeah? Why the fuck did
they get in there first?
Who?This is fucking bullshit!
They're getting dibs
on all the good shit.
Oh, fuck me.
Those are our fucking Furbies.
Mitch, what the hell
are you doing?
I didn't let them in.
You think I let them in?Come on, man.
What are they doing
in there, man?
You fucking better let us in
right fucking now.
All right, everybody,
just stay calm please.
Fuck you!
Just push back
and stay calm, everybody.
Doug, lock it up. Now.Yeah.
Guys, nobody's getting in.
We're locking the doors.
Stay calm and back up!
We need you to push back
a little bit.
Hold this for me.Fuck you, bitch. Hey, hey.
Hey, store's open, everyone.Hey, give me that.
We need backup immediately!
Step right up,
get your fucking waffle irons!
Hold up.
Manny, I need help!
Oh, my God.
Dude.The fuck is happening?
What the fuck is going on?
Fuck this shit!
Manny! Manny, help!Fuck!
Where the fuck are you going?
Hey, back the fuck up,
back the fuck up.
Open the door. They're gonna
get crushed. Open it.
You have to open the door.
You have to get to Mitch.
Get Mitch, Doug.
You have to get to him.
Okay, yeah, I'll open it.AMANDA: Oh, my God.
Jess, Jess, call your dad.
Jess, call your dad right now.Give me your phone.
Yo, open the door!Give me your fucking phone.
They're gonna get crushed.
Open the fucking door.
What are you doing?Open the fucking door!
Yeah, yeah, okay. Yeah, yeah.
Just gotta find the key.
Looking for the key.
Open the door! Bobby?
Open the fucking door.DOUG: Hold on, calm down.
What is wrong with you?Stop shoving.
Get off of me! Shit!Fuck off! Fuck off!
Back the fuck up!
What the...?
Oh, fuck, back the fuck up!
Back the fuck up!
Go. Go.Oh, my God.
Fucking move.
Lonnie, grab it!
Get off, that's my
fucking waffle iron!
This is fucking gold.
This is fucking crazy.
Gaby, wait...
It's all right.
Jesus Christ.
It's fucking insane!
Evan, what the fuck?
You're gonna fucking die!
No, it's fine. Stay there.Get the fuck down!
What the fuck?
Evan! Evan!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!Evan, get down!
Fuck you!
Got to be hundreds more
in the back!
Move! Get the fuck
out of the way!
Yulia! No. Move!
Get the fuck...
Jess.
He's alive.
Hey! Hey, I'm coming!
No, Bobby. Bobby.Hey.
Hey!Bobby!
Bobby! Bobby!
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
Fuck you! What the fuck?
You fuckstick!Stop it, stop it.
You know,
you're a fucking Muppet!
You Jim Henson motherfucker!
Go back to Fraggle Rock!
Nice jacket,
you Michael Jackson,
you fucking pussy licker!
Fuck you.
Amanda! Amanda!
No. No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, Amanda, no.
No.
Amanda, look at me.
Amanda.
Somebody help me!
Please help me!
Oh, my God.
Oh! Oh, fuck!
Stop!
Evan, get the fuck down!
This is fucking gold.You suck!
Evan, help me!
Evan, help me! Get the...
- Oh, my God. Holy shit.
- What the fuck?
That was crazy.Evan, get the fuck down.
I've never fucking seen
something like this in my life.
It's Thanksgiving,
not Thanksbuying!
I'm live here at Right Mart
and although
the store has announced
they will have substantial
security upgrades
for Thanksgiving,
many residents feel after last
year's catastrophic events,
the store shouldn't
be open at all.
Thomas Wright,
you and your entire family
have blood on your hands.
My wife's blood.
We open for Thanksgiving, you
only hire two security guards?
One of whom runs away and
the other is trampled to death
in the same stampede
that killed my wife.
You and your entire family
need to go to prison.
Not have another sale!
Right Mart owner,
Thomas Wright,
has worked overtime
since last year
to give back to the community,
restoring Plymouth Park
and even going so far
as to start
the Wright Family Foundation,
sending local kids to college.
But many say it's not enough.
Local pitching phenom
Bobby Di Stasi
suffered a career-ending injury
and has not been heard from
since the accident.
Many lawsuits were filed
and settled,
but the security cameras
somehow weren't working
the night of the tragedy.
All I know is the cameras
were functioning perfectly fine
when I arrived.
Then they mysteriously
stopped working
the one night there's an actual
disaster at the store.
How convenient.
Thanks, Mitch.
Reporting live, Hank Morton
at the Right Mart
in downtown Plymouth.
Chet, Natalie, back to you.
And here you go.
Happy Thanksgiving.Yeah.
Good morning, Sheriff.
You want the usual?
Two cups today, Lizzie.
New deputy's coming.
Oh, well,
he was in here yesterday
and, uh, he's not much
for conversation.
Yeah.A real charmer.
Probably just overwhelmed
by the thriving metropolis
that is Plymouth.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, chills... ♪
What the fuck?
Fuck you.
This fish.It's organic.
Oh, you know, all the lobsters
from the north...
Here he is. Good morning.
Good morning, Sheriff.Welcome.
And here you are.
It's John Carver.
He was the first...
First governor
of New Plymouth colony.
Look at you. You've been doing
your homework there, Labelle.
Well, if you call reading
a plaque on a statue homework.
Oh, now, come on,
show some enthusiasm.
Thanksgiving
is an institution here.
What kid wouldn't want
to wear that, right?
Yeah, get used to it.
Everybody's
gonna be wearing them.
Yeah. I can get used to it.
♪ But then I bury
the hatchet. ♪
Yes!
Let's go.
What-what are you doing?
Kid, what are you doing?
I just hit top two rungs.
That means you get to go again.
Somebody keeps tagging me
in the video.
Yeah, they're tagging me, too.
God. I'm gonna report it.
Yeah, but people
keep reposting it.
You think someone's doing
it on purpose?
Dude, I just won
this candy apple.
I hit the bull's-eye
like three times in a row.
Awesome.
Good job, babe.
What?
What is it?
What did I do now?
Evan,
get the fuck down!This.
This is fucking gold.
I thought we were past this.Yeah, so did I.
Well, fuck this.
I'm going back to the axe pit.
It's safer there.
Ev, I'm sorry.
I wasn't the only one
with a phone that night.
I know you didn't post it.
Come on, come on.
Ugh.
I have to go
to the John Carver house
to film that stupid commercial
with my dad.
I'm making
my grandmother's stuffing.
Her secret ingredient
was a touch of eggplant.
I only hope I can make it
half as good as hers, though.
Oh, I'm sure you'll make
an excellent dinner, Kathleen.
Hey, Jessica.Hey.
So, you ready for your
big moment in the limelight?
Oh, yeah. Already wrote
my acceptance speech.
Ah, I have mine ready, too.
Yours?
Didn't your father tell you?
He wants a family commercial
this year.
Look at it this way:
One more year until college.
How am I supposed to have
an answer? I don't...
I can't fucking believe this!
I don't have an answer, Stan.
I have no idea
what in the hell just happened.Huh.
Don't know what he's doing.
It's now just
a complete disaster.
What's going on?You got to see this.
This is a fucking disaster.
The whole commercial's ruined.
I've been screaming
at everybody the whole morning.
Okay, guys, back up.
I got to call this in.
Yeah, a historical landmark
has been trashed.
What?
Yeah, whatever.
That, too.
I got to shut this place down.
I catch these guys,
I'm gonna prosecute them
for vandalism.
Uh, yeah, and theft.
Because there was an axe
on that wall I was gonna use.
It's gone.
Come to Right Mart,
where we slash prices...
without a fucking axe!
My commercial's ruined.
You look relieved.
Yeah.
I'm tired of pretending
like everything's normal
when it's not.
Well, hey, Jess, I want things
to go back to normal, too.
That's why this year's
gonna be everything
last year was supposed to be.
Dad...
Having another sale
like nothing happened
doesn't change anything.
It just ignores it.
And as usual, we can't have
one moment alone.
Hey.Hey.
I'm good. Very good.
How are things going
with Jessica?
Dude, they're amazing.
She invited me to the parade
to be on the float,
and then I scored an invite
to Thanksgiving dinner
with her family at her house.
I feel like I'm in.
Bobby ghosting her is the best
thing that ever happened to me.
Nicely played.
Is this good?
♪ I know what boys like... ♪
McCarty Party.
That is where you want to be.
You look like you enjoy alcohol
and drinking,
so you're gonna want to come
down to the McCarty party.
25 whole dollars. Hey.
You guys want tickets
to McCarty Party?
I can do a group rate.
He's charging this year?Yeah.
He's been watching
a lot of "Shark Tank."
Dude thinks he's Mark Cuban.
No, thank you.
Selling alcohol to teens
isn't exactly disrupting.
No, but it is
a recession-proof business.
Let me know
if you guys want tickets.
They're selling out quick.How about you
finish my fucking history paper,
and then we'll talk tickets?
Sure.SCUBA: You're an asshole.
You're such... Be nicer to him.
Listen, listen.GABY: He's a sweetie.
Gabs.EVAN: I paid him
a pretty decent sum of money.
What? I can't write papers and
play football at the same time.
Are you kidding?It's Bobby.
Oh, shit. He's back.
Wait, why didn't he come talk
to you?
I don't know. I haven't talked
to him in, like, a year.
Yeah, that's definitely him.
I don't think so.
♪ I know what boys like ♪
♪ I know what's
on their mind... ♪
"The table is set"?
This is weird.
No, it's-it's a fake.
He has no followers.EVAN: Ooh, it's a table.
We're all tagged.
Mm, Ryan's here.
Evan.
Can you at least try and seem
like you're not a dick?
I'm nice to him.
Okay? Ryan's fine.
He just...
He's harmless, like an NPC.
But...
he messes with
the group dynamic.
Okay.GABY: Just be nicer.
For me.Okay. I just have nothing
to talk about with the guy.
He's just, like...
He's kind of boring.
Well, maybe if you made
a bit of an effort.
I mean, he's a good guy.
Good guy.
Well, he hasn't just ghosted me
yet, so...
he's frontrunner.
NPC.
Hey.Walks like a robot.
Talks like a robot.
What's up, everyone?Ryan!
Hey!
How you doing?Hello!
Hi, Gab. Good to see you.Good to see you.
You finish your paper?
Barely.
I had to start another one
today, and I got...
I'm gonna just... I'm gonna be
swamped until Christmas,
let's just say that.
That's crazy, bro.
Oh, excuse me.
We're ready to order.
This isn't Right Mart, honey.
You actually have
to wait your turn here.
Ooh, she told you.
Someone's in trouble.She told us.
Uh, so, what-what are you guys
doing
for the Pats-Steelers game?
Probably watching at my place.
- That sounds fun.
- You can totally do that.
Or...
you could watch it with me
on the 50-yard line.
Wait.SCUBA: What's up? Yo.
Bro, are you serious?I swear. Hey...
Oh, my God.Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yes, sir.That's what's up.
Scuba, you know me.Jess, brownie points.
Very sweet.I-I like this guy.
This guy.
All right.
Are you shits ready to order?
Yes. Uh, can I do
the vanilla frappe?
All right. You want jimmies
on it?
Extra jimmies.
Garlic knots for the table?
Garlic knots.This isn't Papa Gino's, kids.
Evan, get the fuck down!
This is fucking gold.
Fuck. No. No!
Where are my fucking keys?
Where are my fucking keys,
goddamn it?!
Fuck.
Motherfucker!
Watch out. Here we go.
Here we go. Watch out, sir.
Oh, my God.
Cover that body! Cover that up.
Yo, Jacob.
Step into my office.
Uh-huh.
What's with the shades?
I had a late night.Huh.
What were you doing?
Well, I had two essays to write.
I'll hook you up next week.
You said that last month.
Yeah, Ms. Byers better
eat this shit up, okay?
Trust me, Evan,
she couldn't have
written it better herself.
Okay.
You're the man.
Mm. Yeah.Brainiac.
Eat shit.
Oh, fuck!
Guys, John Carver
tagged us again.
Oh, fuck.
Look.
Oh, my God.
These seats are for us.
Our names are at the table.
Stay behind the line.
Oh, Sheriff, what happened?
Is this killing connected
to what happened at Right Mart?
Can we get this pushed back
a little bit?
Am I walking on anything?
What do you got for me?
Guys are going through
security footage inside.
Inside?Sheriff.
Sheriff, can you tell us
anything...
Can you get these guys
out of the way?
Pete.
We found this where
the killer broke in.
What is this?
I think it's brick.
Or pieces of brick.Right.
Labelle, you've met
Detective Chu, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we met.
Come take a look at this.
Brick.
We got the killer
on security cam,
and you're not gonna believe
what he's wearing.
Cameras at Right Mart
caught the same guy
lowering her legs
onto the sign from the roof.
It's just like you said,
Sheriff.
Everyone in town's
wearing them.
Yeah.
Jess, you know me.
I will not be bullied
by some freaking lunatic.
The store is staying open,
and I'm hiring extra security.
But, honey, I need you to get to
the sheriff's office now.
I know. We're going now.Okay, but just ask anyone
who was there that night
to go talk to them.
Okay, okay. Bye.I love you.
He's hiring additional security.
But not closing the store.
Correct.
That would make sense.
Wait. Wait,
are you serious?
Did your dad not see
this guy tagged us?
Is he waiting for us
to be on a fucking display
in front of his store?I'm asking him right now.
Why?Scuba, don't.
Why the fuck not?
He gonna tag me,
I'm gonna send that motherfucker
a DM. Come get me, bitch.
Don't slide
into the killer's DMs.
Scuba, please,
just hold off, okay?
It's a murder case
in my dad's store.
We can't just fuck around.Fuck around and find out.
Fuck around and find out.SCUBA: That's right.
He'll see
what happens.
Are you crazy, McCarty?Come on, princess.
I wouldn't hit you.
You know how much paperwork
the cops
would make me fill out?
McCarty, are you back
to finish tenth grade?
I just thought, you know,
in light of the current
situation,
you might want
a little "protection."
Courtesy of my old man's store.
McCarty, only you
would have the balls
to sell guns
at a high school.
I should kick your ass right
here.
Come on, Mark Cuban would
think I'm a fucking genius:
Everyone gets a gun,
problem solved.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, Scooby snacks.
Jesus, I'm only kidding.
I wouldn't sell guns to kids.
I'm selling alcohol.
And right now I gotta meet
that little farthead Jacob
to sell him some more
McCarty Party tickets.
All right, McCarty.Okay.
Sales are going
through the roof.
Fuck off, McCarty.No one's coming to that.
You guys should comeYULIA: You're a creep.
It's the only place in town
you won't get killed.
I could really use
your help, Jessica.
Uh, okay, what can I do?
We've exhausted
pretty much every resource
to identify people, but anyone
involved with that night
could be in serious danger.
I knew I shouldn't have
let them in the store.
Detective, can you
give us a moment?
Yes.
If you look closely,
you can see all our names.
And-and then it's kind
of blurry, it says "Scuba."
Why do they call you Scuba?
My last name's Dybing.
What's your first name?
Claude.
Yeah, Scuba's better.
Jessica, you know,
I don't know what happened
with those cameras last year,
but at this point,
I don't care.
Because I understand you're
in a difficult situation.
But I know you want
to do the right thing.
So if you know something,
anything that can help us
with the information
on that night,
I promise I'll keep it
between us.
Because this is a matter
of life and death.
Jess.
Saw you at the Cap yesterday.
No. I got in this morning.
You working for your uncle
again?
I'm helping out
while I'm in town.
Well, I'm sure
I'll see you around.
Hey, Jess, wait.
I'm sorry.
Can I walk with you?
I mean, you ghosted me.
You're off social media.
You deleted every trace
of yourself.
I ghosted everybody.
Yeah, but I'm not everybody.
I was your girlfriend.
I blamed you for
what happened to me,
and instead of just
telling you about it,
I vanished, like a dick.
I feel so stupid now,
but I just...
Bobby, I feel horrible.
If I hadn't let you guys in...No, don't.
Don't.
It-it was my decision.
I could have
stayed outside.
It's not your fault.
How's your arm?
I mean,
rehab's going great,
so I might get back up to
full-speed pitching again.
Golden Arm.Yeah.
That's good.
I'm happy to hear it.
Hey. What is it?
Nothing.
You know, I'm still your friend.
You can trust me.
That night,
after the trampling,
Kathleen was in a panic,
ranting about
bad publicity
and getting sued, and...
she went into the security room
and deleted all the footage.
She asked me not
to say anything,
and I didn't stop her.
There's nothing you can
do about it now, so...
That's the thing.
Maybe there is.
Look, there's a backup system
at my house
in my dad's office.
Jess, that's probably long gone.
No, it stores the footage
for a year.
Then tell your dad you need it,
and then,
given the circumstances,
he prob...No, no, no, no.
With the lawsuits, no way.
He's pretending like
it doesn't exist.
Well, what do you want to do?
I want to see what's on it.
Thanks for talking.
Yeah. It was really nice.
Oh, no, don't turn around.
It's Ryan Baker.
I'll get rid of him.
Hi, babe.Hi.
How you doing? All right?Yeah, yeah, fine.
Did you, um,
give your statement?
Yeah, I did, but they were
just looking to
identify people, and I didn't
know anybody except Scott,
so I didn't have much
to offer.
How you doing,
Bobby?
Well, I'm sorry to
break up this reunion,
but, uh, Bobby, could I see you
in my office?
This is new.
Yep. A lot's changed
since you left.
Looks like it.
All right,
let's get out of here.
Still no suspects
in the brutal murder of
local waitress Lizzie McMullan.
Authorities have no clues
other than cryptic
social media posts,
leaving many residents to wonder
who will be the next victim
of John Carver.
Hey, Dewey.
Hey, buddy, Daddy's going
on a little vacation.
All right? Going down to
the Dominican Republic,
and Gina's gonna
come down her, all right.
You just chill, buddy.
Who the fuck is...
Hey. Yeah.
I'm waiting.Yeah, man, I see you.
I got a fucking flight.
I'll be there in a minute.
All right?
Jesus.
All right, buddy.
Fuck.
Fuckin' passport.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Fuck.
Show yourself!
I'm a security guard.
I kill people every fucking day!
Hey, I'm not scared
of you, buddy.
Don't fuck with me!
Let's fuckin' go!
Dewey. Dewey where is he?
Where is he?
Tell Daddy where he is, Dewey.
Is he that way?
Night, Mom.
Our killer has claimed
a second victim.
He's brazen, confident.
He's spent a considerable
amount of time and energy
setting this up, but none
of this works unless he has
a private location where
he's taking the victims.
He's powering off his phone
so we can't track him
on the move.
He's taking the picture
and then uploading it
from another location.
We have one bit of physical
evidence that leads us
to Cordage Park.
Effective immediately,
we're searching
every inch of it.
Hey.Oh, hi, Dad.
I was just using your computer.Oh, it's fine. Listen...
I've been thinking
a lot about what you said.
You know, after Mom died,
the only thing that I
could do to survive was work.
Because it's all I know.
But work...
doesn't fill the void.
So, when I met Kathleen,
I felt alive again.
I was...
willing to just
overlook all flaws
and it might've...
been at your expense.
And I just want to say...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Love you, Dad.
Love you.
You find anything?
Yeah. Let's go.
Wait, what is it?
Nothing. Let's just go.
I know this kid.
Lionel. He goes to our school.
He's always the turkey
in the parade.
And I-I know that guy.
He goes to Hanover South.
Evan punched him, remember?JESSICA: Yeah,
he's the one
who started the riot.
He had the bullhorn.
I think his name is...
Larry? Or Lonnie?
Or-Or something.
And she's probably
a cheerleader.
That's great, Bobby. Thank you.
Yeah.
Hey, w-what is it?
There's one more.
That's Ryan Baker.
He didn't know anyone
other than his roommate, huh?
And that's Doug.
The guard that got
crushed to death.
Jessica, did Ryan ever mention
to you that he knew Doug?
Because that certainly
wasn't in his statement.
No.
Yeah.
There may not be anything to it.
Be careful who you trust.
Both of you.
Yeah, don't worry.
I'll take care of Ryan today.
You're not taking care
of anything.
He just said
it could be nothing.
All right, fine, Jess.
If I see Ryan, I'll act
like nothing's weird.
For you.
You should get back to school.
But stay alert.
That's why I won't be
celebrating Thanksgiving
this year or any year.
You're so brave.So brave.
Thank you, Chad.
That was very inspiring.
Next up...
Mr. Fletcher.
Let's go, Fletcher.
All right.
Um...
the piece that I have written...
uh, is titled "The Wampanoag
and the Native American Side
of Thanksgiving,"
by Evan Fletcher.
"While today Thanksgiving
"is one of our nation's
favorite holidays,
"it has a very different meaning
"for many Native Americans.
"For the Wampanoag,
Thanksgiving is a day
of mourning."
That was beautiful, Evan.
I enjoyed hearing you read it.
As much as I enjoyed
writing it for my blog.
I'm gonna kill
that little asswipe.
If it makes you feel
any better, you'll probably
be killed before you get
suspended for plagiarism.
Scuba. Don't even joke
about that.
Yeah, my bad, you're right.
Plagiarism's serious.
When did you talk to him last?
Two days ago.GABY: Was there a reason?
Yeah, there's a reason.
I never bought Ryan's
Mr. Perfect routine.
Yeah, I mean, how would he
know a random security guard
and why would he not
tell anybody?
I don't know.
Doug just moved here.
He was the new guy.
This guy have any family
in Plymouth?
I think his family's
in Nebraska.
I-I don't believe
for a second it was Ryan.
Doesn't make sense.
He's too nice.
Okay,
let's not be naive here.
I mean, the nicest guys
are the most psycho,
they're just better
at hiding it.
God, what is wrong with me?YULIA: It's not you.
Nothing wrong with you, Jess.
I feel like I can't
trust anybody.
You're probably right.
I mean, us.
It's all we got right now.
And, yes, I am excluding Bobby.
Bobby?
Wh... Bobby would never.
I told you, he was doing great.
No, you told us he told you
he was doing great.
That's different
than he's doing great.
For all we know,
he's not even at school,
and he's driving around
in that tow truck full time.
Wait, hey, hey. Why are we
even talking about them?
It's got to be Mitch. I mean,
he's obsessed with the store,
his wife just died,
and he hates us.
That's right! Yo, that guy's
up to his eyeballs in motive.
And he drives a van:
the official transportation
choice for pedophiles,
kidnappers, rapists,
murderers...
Yep, yep, you're right,
you're right.
Scuba.
Like Coach Ingalls says,
the best defense
is a good offense.
Me and you, we go after them,
fuck them up one by one.Let's go, let's go.
And we'll get some, we'll get
some help from McCarty's store.
Guys. Evan. Babe.
This is not a game, okay?
These are not some Hanover kids.
Can we just let the police
handle it, Ev?
We're in deep shit here.
We let the police handle it,
we're all gonna end up 50% off.
Are you gonna answer it?
No.
This fits.
You're on the Right Mart
"Mayflower"?
Yep.
Next.
Bobby boy.
Forgotten, but not gone.
Forgotten?
It feels like I never left.
You in the parade now?
Yeah, Jess asked me.
Newlon was right, you know.
A lot has changed
since you left.
Ah, maybe not as much
as you think.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, no, I just mean that I'm
helping with the parade again.
Hmm.
You know, if you weren't
leaving in a few days,
I would knock your teeth out.
Whoa, leaving?
Buddy...
Who says I'm leaving?
You fucking pussy.
You fucking want it.
Let's fucking go.
One more. One more!
There you fucking go! Nice!
The fuck's going on here?
Come on, Hanover.
We gonna carve up Plymouth
like a turkey tomorrow or what?
Let's go! Harder!
Harder! One more time!
Fuck yeah!
Looking good, cover girl.
Nice. Nice. Nice form, there.
Good shit.
♪ Mysteries of the days
of old ♪
♪ You'll find the key,
you got the gold ♪
Uh, listen, you guys
keep going, okay?
Neil, burpees after this,
all right? You're in charge.
♪ One, two, three lock box ♪
♪ One, two, three lock box. ♪
Where the fuck we are going?
Shh.
Coach has strict orders,
all right?
No sex.
Just a little tease.
Sit.
What, here?
What?
You're fucking crazy,
you know that?
Are you ready?
Fucking born ready.
Jesus.
Are you sure?
Here we go!
Fucking cancelled?
What the fuck?Relax.
You can't cancel my game!
You heard the man.
Let's go, Fletcher.
Game's getting rescheduled.
Let's get changed.
Rescheduled until when?
Until when?
June?Someone's missing.
I'm gonna be fucking
graduated by then, bro!
Where you going?I'm gonna go play,
that's what I'm gonna do!
Dude, you can't play
football alone, dumbass.
Watch me!
Blunderbuss!
McCarty, what the fuck
are you doing?
I was just gonna fire it off
if they won the game.
It's just fucking gunpowder,
it's all right.
Sorry, Sheriff.
My kid's a fucking idiot.
He's a fucking goober chucker.McCARTY'S DAD: Get in the car,
you fucking idiot.God, I hate those things.
I can't even smell the powder.
First commercial
my dad made me do,
he took it so seriously
he insisted I learn
how to pack it.
He made me do it
over and over again.
Almost blew up in my hand.
Jess, you should go home.
Gaby, maybe go find Evan,
get him out of here.
I heard they found blood.
Yeah.
The people missing
were at the Right Mart.
You stay together,
or at least in pairs, okay?
Okay, yeah.Shit.
I'll go get him.Okay, I'll meet you inside.
Hey, I can leave, you guys.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let's go back together.
Hmm? We'll be right back.
Yeah, wait up.Okay.
Okay.
That's weird.
Gabs.
Gaby?
Help! Help!
He's in there! Please help!
Please help!
Did you notice
anything about him?
Um...
He was dressed as a pilgrim.
And-and he had
a John Carver mask on.
Okay. Just think.
It's about the details.
Small mistakes,
that's how they get caught.
I'm sorry, I...
I only saw him
for a few seconds.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay. Don't be sorry.
Okay.Okay, we're gonna get you home.
You're doing great.Okay.
Thank you. All right.
You guys good?Yeah.
We got to get you guys
home soon, okay?
Get out of here.
Hey, Bobby's coming.
Hey, is she...? Hey.
Are you okay?
Here, here, here.
Thanks.
That's my girlfriend. Jess.
He came right for me.Did you see him?
Hi.RYAN: You okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
He came after me,
but I got away.
Douche.
That's been happening
a lot here recently.
I wonder why.
Okay, you want to tell us
about your little buddy,
the security guard?
I'm sorry, who?Dude, stop lying to her, man.
Just like how
you lied to the cops.
Going to the corner,
huddled together?
I'm sorry, are you talking
about the security guard
from-from Right Mart? Doug?
We have proof.
It's on video, dude.
You are a fucking idiot, man.
I honestly hope
you make a better pitcher
than you do a detective.
No, I walked off with him
because we were getting addies.
That's why Scott was there.
I was just bro-ing up with him
'cause I needed another hookup.
Adderall?"Adderall?"
Yes, Adderall.
That is what smart kids do,
so we can get into Ivy League
schools, and guys like you
can tow our Porsches.Get your...
Bitch!Hey, hey, hey.
Yo, what the fuck?Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Get the fuck off.Ryan!
Get home, both of you.
I didn't...And stay the fuck away
from the parade tomorrow.
I see either one of you
on the street,
I'm gonna haul you both in.
Jess, I'm not the bad guy here.Go.
He came at me.This isn't done.
He just, he just came at me.No. Stop!
Stop!
I can't believe you two.
My friends could be dead,
and you can't put
your bullshit aside?
I don't want to see
either of you.
Okay?
Get out.Jess, that is not what...
Get out!
Shit. It's my dad.
Yulia.
Yulia, come.
I... I...
Papa. Get in.
What are you doing? Pop.
Get in the Mercedes. Dad!
Just tell me where we're going.Florida.
He's just taking her
to Florida?
I don't know.
That's about as much
of a conversation
I've ever had with the guy.
What?
Evan's right.
The police ain't doing shit.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
McCARTY:
Ladies and gentlemen,
another satisfied customer.
Jacob, get him a T-shirt.
Here you go, buddy.
On the house.
Hey, listen, I just
want to know if it's worth it
before we pay.
I mean, I heard this party
isn't even all that, so...
Listen, kid.
Sometimes things end up much
better than you'd expect,
all right?
Think of it this way,
when Black Sabbath
fired Ozzy in '79,
you would've figured
it was all fucking over.
The end of an era.
But then, along comes
Ronnie James Dio,
all five foot nothing of him,
the evil little elf,
and he brought a magic
to that band
that they hadn't seen in years.
Who's Black Sabbath?
Get the fuck off my property.
I just want to know.
Who's Black...
Get the fuck off
my property right now.
Go back to Methuen,
you fucking dorks.
Fuck you.No virgins allowed.
McCARTY:
Cocksucker.
Jacob. VIP. Upstairs. Now.
All right.
♪ Will he survive, will he
survive, will he survive ♪
♪ Will he survive the sword? ♪
Watch out, this kid's
been here for two days.
Drank too much white zinfandel.
Welcome to the Death Star.
This is where the magic happens.
Jacob, VIP's closed.JACOB: Yeah.
McCARTY:
You're on door patrol.
You get caught with any of
this shit, you're on your own.
Jesus, Scuba.What about this?
That's mainly for taking down
angry grizzlies
in the Alaskan wilderness
or brain-eating zombies
in a post-apocalyptic America.
All right.
Let me show you something
far more reasonable.
.44 Magnum. A classic.
Plus, you get bonus points
if you make
a Dirty Harry-style comment
when you blast him.
Mc-McCarty, do you have
any human-sized guns?
Maybe.
All right.
The SIG 226.
It's a short recoil-operated,
locked breech pistol.
Decent stopping power.
You'll want to use this.
Keep the safety on,
unless you want
to blow your nuts off.
What about you, Right Mart?
Uh, I fired a musket once.
It almost killed me.
Yeah, those things are fucked.
Let me show you something.
Check this out.
Element of surprise, huh?
Pull it out of your belt
and you stick 'em
right in the gut.
We got all sorts
of tactical shit.
It's yours if you want it.
Um, I'm-I'm good.
Scuba will be with me,
and he's armed, so...
All right.
McCarty, I owe you one.
Yeah. Anytime.
All right. Thanks.
Yeah.
Scuba. Jess.
Be careful out there, huh?
Keep yourself alive long enough
to return that thing.
I don't know what you think
you're gonna do with a gun.It's for protection, baby.
You've never even
held one before.
You've never seen one before.
If you really want someone
to come and help,
I'm sure my dad can, like,
call the sheriff's department
and send a cop over.
There's one here right now.
Hey, can I come by?
Um, okay, I'm packing right now
'cause I'm going to Florida,
apparently, so...
Okay, I don't know
when I'll be back,
but I'm a little stressed, okay?
I'll call you back later.
Okay. Call me from the car.
Geez.
For you. Enjoy.
Thank you. You sure?
Eat it.
We are going to Florida.
Appreciate it.
When's the, uh,
the remodel done?
Never.
Dad?
Dad!
Jesus, Dad.
What the hell?
Car is coming. Finish.
Okay. Trying to.
Fucking contact.
What the hell?
Yulia!
Dad, I'm coming.
Jesus, what now?
Hey, baby.
Hey, what's up?
My dad's, like, freaking out
at me right now.
We have to leave in, like,
five minutes.
Okay, yeah, yeah,
no problem, uh...
Okay. Well, I'll call you
from the car.
I love you.
Fuck! Fuck!
Scuba, go!SCUBA: No!
Yulia!
No! Fuck no!Yulia!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No!SCUBA: No! Fuck!
Yulia!Fuck!
Dad! Dad!
No, no, no. No, no, no.
No, no!
Yulia! Yulia!Yulia!
Oh, fuck. Yulia!
Scuba! Hurry up! Hurry!Yulia!
Scuba!
Yulia!Yulia!
Scuba, help me.
Let her fucking go.Scuba, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let her fucking go, or I'll
blow your fucking head off!
He has Gaby and Evan.
They're alive.
Fuck.
What do I do, Jess?Where are they?
Please, Scuba, please.
Where are they?Jess, what do I do?
I don't know! I don't know!
Listen,
let her fucking go.
Shoot him.
Shoot him, please, please.
Let her fucking go!Scuba! Scuba.
Stop!Shoot him! Shoot him now!
Scuba. Scuba, the safety.
Take off the safety.SCUBA: Fuck!
What do I...
what do I do, Jess?
Jess, what do I do?
It doesn't seem real. I mean,
I-I can't even believe
this is really happening.
How does this happen
in a place like this?
I mean, is there any...
Like, what are they...
What do you do?
Somebody need to call SWAT?
I mean, have you ever?
I mean, maybe we should move.
I-I don't want to move.
I love this house.
We're not moving. It's
not even a possibility to move.
They're not gonna
let me... I-I just need...
I just need...
Give me a couple of seconds.
I just think
we're all in agreement
that we're not gonna be
participating in the parade.
I'm with you, Thomas.
Well, I know I'm not going.
It's too dangerous.
And it's not dangerous
for Gaby and Evan?
You saw what he did to Yulia.
I can't let that
happen to them.
We have to stop him.
This parade is our chance
to catch him.
If we hide, then what?
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life
looking over my shoulder.
Do you?
You're right, Jess.
I'm in. Let's do this.KATHLEEN: Look.
Right Mart has extra security,
so we don't have to worry
about the store. Okay?
And as far as I'm concerned,
the parade has been decided.
God, I do not want to be
dragged into this any further.
I mean, if you hadn't even gone
into the store,
this would've never happened.
Enough, Kathleen.Don't you mean you?
You're the one who wanted
to open the store.
Nobody was
"Nostra-fucking-damus"
to predict what happened
last year.
Besides, this year,
I'm closing the store.
Thanksgiving's a holiday,
even for us.
Wait, honey, what?
Kathleen,
it's the right thing to do.
I made the decision.
It's final.
Sheriff, is there a way
to set a trap?
Well...
when the float returns
to the warehouse,
we can make it
look like it's empty.
Make him think there's
an opportunity to strike.
And if he takes the bait,
it'll be over
right there and then.
The bait?
Excuse me, I don't want us
being used as bait.
We don't finish it now, we'll
be bait no matter where we go.
My daughter's right.
Tomorrow, John Carver
is gonna go down.
All right, Lionel, turkey time.
Here we go.
I want two people
up here to keep an eye on that.
Over here as well.
See this whole section?
Keep an eye on that for me,
will you? Hey.
Hey.Okay, when you get back here,
this place is gonna look empty,
but I'm gonna be here,
and this whole place
will be crawling
with officers, okay?
Yup. Thank you, Sheriff.You're welcome.
Hi.
Thank you for coming.Mm.
You ready?
No.Good.
Me neither. Let's do this.
Okay.
Hey, Jess.
Uh...
What's this?
Oh, it's my dad's ring
from Iraq.
He said it kept him alive.
Uh, i-if you want,
wear it for good luck.
Thank you.You're welcome.
Happy Thanksgiving!
Hi.
Pilgrims!
Happy Thanksgiving!
Down with Right Mart!
What's going on?
What the hell
is going on down there?
It's Mitch.
Get off the parade route.
Get off!
Get off! Move along.
Come on, come on.It's nothing. Okay.
Happy Thanksgiving.
You have a great day.
Happy Thanksgiving!
Happy Thanksgiv...
Grandpa, Grandpa, watch out!
Stop the truck!
Watch out!
Come on.LABELLE: Go, go.
Go.
Wake up! Grandpa! Wake up!Grandpa, wake up! Wake up!
Grandpa, wake up! Grandpa!Wake up! Wake up!
Come on, get in, get in,
get in, get in, get in!
Get in! Go, go, go, go, go!
In, in, in, in, in!Oh, shit.
Get us out of here.
Cover your ears.
♪ The house is haunted by the
echo of your last goodbye ♪
memories that refuse to die ♪
♪ I can't get away
from the vision that brings ♪
♪ Intimate glimpses
of intimate things ♪
♪ A voice in my heart
like a torch singer sings ♪
♪ I wonder who is
kissing her now ♪
♪ ...cluttered up with roses
that have lived too long ♪
♪ Much too long... ♪
- Shh. He's right there.
- He's right...
He's coming. He's right there.
Please be quiet.
Shh. Please.
I'll be right back.
No.
Don't leave.I'll come back. I'll come back.
Be quiet. Be quiet. Shh.
Don't leave.I'll come back.
Don't leave. No.
No. No! No!
Help me! Let me out!
No.
No, no, no.
No. No!
No! No.
No!
Help me. Please don't kill me,
please.
Please!
Open the door! Open the...
Please, please don't do this.
Please.
Please, I'm begging you, please!
No!
No. No! No! No! Please.
No, please!
No!
No! Please!
No... No!
No! No!
I'm live outside the Plymouth
Sheriff's Department
where outraged citizens
are demanding answers
after a performer was murdered
in broad daylight
at the Thanksgiving Day Parade.
Flash grenades,
smoke bombs.
I think he's ex-military.
Could be.
There's no way
he's in a civilian car.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I-I got something.
What do you got?
He's live streaming
from somewhere in Cordage Park.
What the fuck is that?
Labelle, let's go.
I'll try to lock the
coordinates in. Calling SWAT.
I need SWAT and all units
at Cordage Park, immediately.
There's nothing here.
We're in a parking lot.
It's telling me
you're in the exact spot.
I'm telling you,
there's fuck all here.
I don't see nothing.
This way.Fuck!
Are there tunnels underneath us?
We'll each take an exit.
Labelle, you take Water Street
and Mayflower.
I'll take Green and Union.
You guys take Doten Street.
SWAT's gonna flush him out.
Got it?
Okay? Let's go.
You'll be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Go, go, go! Take it down!
On three.Ready?
Two lines, two columns.
Copy.
Go, go. Cover my six.
Copy that.
Closing in on the signal.
Go, go, go!
Break it in.Copy.
Did you find them?
Give me a sitrep.
What the fuck?
It's a fucking monitor.
Damn.
He's using a new cell.
Gather 'round.
No, no, no. No.
Gather 'round the table,
everyone.
Dinner is served.
Goddamn.
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck?
Now, is that any way
to thank Kathleen?
She's been cooking all day.
Let's start off the dinner
with a cheer
from our cheerleader.
Fresh from my wine refrigerator.
She'll pair nicely
with Kathleen.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
You might want to
let that breathe.
So nice to all be together
again on Thanksgiving.
And joining us...Dad!
Our guest of honor,
Thomas Wright,
who missed last year's fun
sitting in his mansion.
Hmm.
Now...
we're all going to go
around the table
and say what we're thankful for.
You're on live,
so choose your words wisely.
Evan.
No, no, no, no, no. No, Ev.
Most appropriate that
you go first.
You see, it was your video
that inspired me to make my own.
Okay.
Evan!
No.
Help! Help!
We're-we're in an old house!Let him go!
Let him go!
So get ready, Evan.No, no, no, no.
You're about to go viral.Please don't kill me...
You're going to
break the Internet.
Let him go!No!
No one appreciates subtlety
anymore.
To go viral,
you really need to hit people
over the head.
Right, Evan?
Mm.
Look at all those likes.
Congratulations, Evan.
You're a star.
Now that I have
your attention...
you're probably wondering
why you're still alive
and they were all killed.
They were just greedy.
But you...
you're the VIPs.
It wasn't enough to get
in the store early.
You had to
taunt everyone outside
to show them
how special you were.
Well, once this video
goes viral,
everyone will know
how special you are.
Too bad you won't be alive
to see it.
This will be the most famous
Thanksgiving dinner
since 1621.
And every year,
people will watch this video...
and think of your greed
and the people who died from it.
Now, let's eat.
Thomas.
You love your consumers.
Well, tonight's your night
to be one.
Take a bite of your lovely wife
and show me
how thankful you are.
Show me that you're thankful...
or die.
Oh, fuck!
Go, go, go!
Run! Go!
Go, go, go!Run! Run!
This way!
Oh, fuck!
Watch out!
Scuba!
Scuba, this way, this way, go.
It's the Carver House.The door, door.
Jess, go, go, go.
Sheriff?
Sheriff.
It's me.
Give me the gun.
It's Bobby.
It's Bobby. It's Bobby.
He went that way.Okay, get outside, get outside.
Get outside. Just get out.
Come on.He went that way.
No. No.
He's in there.No.
I think I shot him.
No.Then I lost him.
All clear here.
Check over there.
Oh, sir.
Detective Chu says you need
to turn in your service weapon
since it's been fired.
Right, right. Yeah, of course.Sorry, pal.
No, don't worry about it.
I understand.
Sheriff,
we, uh, found this on the floor.
Still logged
into the John Carver account.
Thanks, Pete.
It's Bobby's.
We have every police officer
in a hundred-mile radius
searching for him.
They, uh...
They had to sedate your father
pretty heavily.
He'll be in the hospital a few
days, along with your friends
Gaby and Scuba.
I'm... sorry
about Kathleen and Evan.
Labelle.
Chu, see you at the hospital.
We'll be there in a minute.
See you there.
We'll see you there, Sheriff.
You're really brave, you know.
Thank you.
Couldn't have done this
without you.
Can you just give me a minute
to catch my breath,
and then... and then we can go?
Yeah, sure.
I'll be right back.
You ready?
It's about the details.
Small mistakes,
that's how they get caught.
I could really use
your help, Jessica.
Couldn't have
done this without you.
But you got to be careful
who you trust.
Jess, you okay?
S-Sorry.
Um...
I'm-I'm not feeling well.
We'll have a doctor
check you out.
Come on.
If only you'd be stuck
on the fence a second longer.
It's like fumbling
on the one-yard line.
It's almost funny
if you really think about it.
You should see the look
of surprise on your face.
What about Bobby?
Bobby?
I had him drugged,
dressed up,
ready to be shot,
putting an end to the mystery
of John Carver's identity.
But when I opened the trunk,
he popped me with a tire iron.
Thankfully,
you pointed me
in the right direction...
again.
You've been using me...
this whole time?
When I said, I couldn't
do this without your help,
I really meant it.
Why?
Why... are you doing this?
Mm.
Mitch wasn't the only one
who lost someone that night.
My wife left me,
and Amanda put me back together.
I loved her.
She was gonna leave Mitch.
But then, you and your friends
took her from me.
You took my family from me.
So now, instead of spending
Thanksgiving with Amanda,
I am stuck here in this office.
And now, so are you.
I'd love to keep chatting,
but now, I got to take care
of some loose ends.
Wait.
I-I didn't get to tell you
what I was thankful for.
What are you thankful for?
The service in here.
You should see the look
of surprise on your face.
You fucking bitch.
Jess.
Hey. Come on.Bobby?
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Hey, come on, come on.Oh, wait. Wait.
Aw, fuck.
Look. Your uncle's truck.
Jessica?!JESSICA: Shh.
Shh. Get down.
Sorry, Jessica.
This year, there will be...
no... leftovers!
When I told your stepmother,
she would make
an excellent dinner...
that... was not...
a lie!
Go.
This way. Come on. Come on.
Oh.
Bobby?!
Bobby!
No!
Bobby, go!Come on, come on, come on.
It's the... it's the cable.
I'm trying to drive.
It's not moving.
Hey, Sheriff, you were right!
No... leftovers!
Jessica!
Roger on unit 121.
Come here.
Take care of yourself.
I'll call you from school.
Be safe.Yeah.
Tell Ryan he's still a dick,
even if he's not the killer.
Oh, Jess.
Hey.
I thought you guys were
at the hospital.
We technically still are.
We saw the stream.
Detective. We searched
every inch of that place.
Everything was incinerated.
There's nothing but ash.
No one could survive a blast
like that.
You okay?
Sorry.
♪ We walk the streets
at night ♪
♪ We go where eagles dare ♪
♪ They pick up every movement ♪
♪ They pick up every loser ♪
♪ With jaded eyes
and features ♪
♪ You think they really care ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better think
about it, baby ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better think about it,
baby, babe ♪
♪ An omelet of disease
awaits your noontime meal ♪
♪ Her mouth of germicide
seducing all your glands ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better think
about it, baby ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better think about it,
baby, baby ♪
♪ With jaded eyes
and features ♪
♪ You think they really care ♪
♪ Let's go where eagles dare,
we'll go where eagles dare ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better think
about it, baby ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better
think about it, baby ♪
♪ I ain't no goddamn
son of a bitch ♪
♪ You better think about it,
baby, bae, bae, bae. ♪
Love you, Dad.Love you.
Cut.