Uploaded by sookantv.com
That's them in there,
just like that? Just like that.
We'll go in there for a day or two.
And the expression kick the hornet's nest?
I'll stay right here, thank you.
Those things scare me to death.
They've been killing my honeybees.
You guys unchecked?
Wipe up the whole colony.
What are you gonna do with them?
Well, that's between me
and them, if you don't mind.
That's okay. I understand these things.
I just wanted to thank
you for putting up with me.
And all of my bees.
This place was crabgrass and
weeds, and you brought it back to life.
Well, you're a blessing.
No one's ever taken care of me before.
Well, uh...
Mr. Clay, come back at
supper time, let me feed you.
Ross, got something? I got one.
I want it.
I need it.
Hey, free my ear.
Get this fucking ear.
If you shut down, please.
United Data Group, good afternoon.
This is Boyd.
How may I help you? Boyd.
Uh, hello.
I just got a message saying that
there's a problem with my computer.
Don't you worry.
The message you received is from our
United Data Group Antivirus Operator.
It's part of the software package
that you pre-installed on your computer.
I'm sorry, I'm not a computer person.
What did you say the name
of your product is again?
Now, our records show that you actually
have an older version on your account,
so what I'm going
to need you to do is
uninstall that and
install the latest version.
I have no idea how to do that.
My daughter set up everything for me.
Well, I would recommend you take
your computer to an IT specialist.
However, keep in mind
that you will lose all your
data since they'll have
to replace the hard drive.
Yeah!
I'm pretty remote out here.
Everything I have is on the computer.
Okay.
There is actually a
software package that you
can download that
would allow me to reinstall.
Remotely.
Alright. Tell me what to do.
It's okay. Can you type this?
Friendly friend dot net.
Spell it just how it sounds.
Okay. I'm there.
And there should be a button
on your screen that says install.
Again, you click on that button.
I clicked the button.
So you're about to see
some windows open close on
your desktop as I reinstall
the virus shield for you.
Okay! I hope you fucking
clowns are paying attention.
Stick to the script, but not so much
that you sound like a goddamn robot.
Alright?
She has got 10K checking.
Life insurance annuity, Roth
IRA, teacher's pension, and...
Holy fucking shit! Alright.
She is a signatory on a
two million dollar account.
Come on.
This is a fucking charity.
Alright kids.
Let the script mind him again.
My computer is going crazy.
Totally normal.
Just do not touch your keyboard.
Because of this inconvenience, I'm going
to credit back your subscription fees.
How about that?
I've gone ahead and filed it $500.
It's the account ending 020.
Oh, that's not my account.
That's an account that I manage.
You log into that account and verify
the transfer, please, Miss Parker.
Yes, there's... There's
a transfer of $50,000.
Set the hook.
With sympathy.
Miss Parker, I... I
made a terrible mistake.
I was supposed to credit you for
$500, but I know I got a stuff key here.
I don't know if it's my job here.
I got kids.
I got fucking kids.
Oh, I don't want you
to get in trouble, but...
I could wire the amount back.
I wouldn't need a
different password though.
One second.
Now, this is the master
password for all her accounts.
Okay, so we second.
We get it. We zero out everything.
You know, I... I think
I should call the bank.
You know what? You're probably right.
But there goes my job.
And there goes all your data.
My kids.
Pictures are on this computer.
Okay.
Fucking yes!
That is what I am talking about!
Come on!
Subtitle made by Master_Blaster for https://subscene.com/
Oh...
What did I do?
Miss Parker? Don't move.
Don't you fucking move.
Drop the knife.
Hands behind your back.
Slowly.
Get on your knees one knee at a time.
Now, who the fuck are you?
And what are you doing in
my mother's house? Verona.
I'm so sorry.
Well, how do you know him?
The working clear me
is our best and only part.
Clear him?
Agent Parker, I know that's your mother.
I understand that there's a world
where she committed suicide.
Suicide?
You can't be serious.
That woman loved life more than anybody.
I know.
But by all means, let's
just completely ignore
the big white dude in
her house with a knife.
Get in line.
Come on.
It's Clay, right?
Adam Clay?
I don't know much to say.
Mr.
Clay, we just got a couple of questions.
Like, what the fuck were you
doing in my mother's house?
I wasn't bringing her a jar of honey.
A jar of honey?
Who the fuck are you,
Winnie the Pooh? I keep these.
How do you know my mother?
She went some space in the barn from her.
I was signed lease.
But what the fuck were
you doing in her house?
She didn't answer when I knocked.
I knocked at her car in the driveway.
I had to smoke alone when I entered.
You know her.
You're a law enforcement background?
I told you I'd take care of these.
His hands tested negative
for gunshot residue,
but the prints on the
gun were your mother's.
Seems sadly it was suicide.
Mr. Clay, I need you to
apologize for last night.
I realize I may have
been a little aggressive.
That's not understandable.
Could I interest you in
something a bit stronger?
No.
Or I'll sit with you if you like.
I wanted to thank you.
For sitting here in my room.
I tried to stay in her
life as much as I could.
Obviously I could have done a better job.
Being old can be the only thing.
In the same age you used to exist.
She used to matter.
You used to be a part of life.
For the family.
Or the heart, I guess you could say.
There's some British
Isles hiding in your accent.
I was born that.
I hated that she was out here alone.
She wouldn't leave.
There's too many memories.
You know, I think I know why she liked you.
You're just like my brother.
He was a Marasaka Marine Raider.
He was killed a few
years ago, kicking doors.
Because she loved him.
Now he'd move on and
you'd think he invented fire.
Meanwhile I graduated the
FBI Academy and she said,
Oh, that's nice.
She got scammed.
Somebody emptied out all her accounts.
Her savings, her retirement, and
every penny maxed out all her cards.
She was an educator,
director of a charity for kids.
I had two million out of that account.
You know I did it.
I talked to an agent in
our cyber crimes office.
This crew's been operating for two
years and we don't even have names.
And even if we did, good luck building
an indictment that would stand up in court.
Some defense attorney would just
argue that the elderly victim agreed
to wire a complete stranger
his entire life savings.
Taking from an elderly person
is as bad as stealing from a child.
Maybe worse.
Someone that's a child.
Her parents.
People who care are ready to step in.
Someone that's an older person.
Sometimes they'll have
to face the hornets alone.
The scenery goes unnoticed.
Well no one cares.
I care.
And I'm stubborn.
And so help me God, I'm going to
get these motherfuckers who did this.
I need to take care of the hive.
You've been up all night.
The hive is more important.
What are you doing?
I thought you were retired.
I did.
I need a favor.
What kind of favor? A name.
A dress.
Easy.
Not easy.
Even the FBI can't find these people.
Well, we're not the FBI, are we?
Show me the deets and stand by.
Yeah.
You weren't kidding.
This one kicked my butt.
They're routing all over the world.
But you found them.
Sure.
But who are these people?
I want to find out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now how do you think you're going, pal?
This United Day to whom?
Don't know nothing about that.
This is private property
and you're trespassing.
We're going inside.
I want to burn it down.
Yeah, that's not happening, buddy.
You're not going anywhere except
right the fuck back the way you came.
Do you know what they do here?
Buddy, I'm counting to three.
One, two, three.
There.
I did it for you.
You aware this is a criminal outfit?
Scamming the weakest in our society?
Stealing everything they have?
Do you know that's who you work for?
Looking for the call center.
Yeah, you're in the right place.
Sign in here.
Tell any of the companies in
the building to evacuate now.
There's going to be a fire.
Okay, thanks.
Hang up the phone.
Oh, I'm good, buddy.
I'm just doing my thing.
Hang up the phone.
Uh, this is Perkins.
So sorry, I don't
want to... You want...
Need your attention, please.
Beat after me.
I will never steal from the
weak, the vulnerable again.
I think I sent you an important download,
and we'll find out what's going on.
Beat after me.
I will never steal from the
weak, the vulnerable again.
To help you keep that promise.
Now we're going to burn
this place to the ground.
Might be a good time to go home.
Hey!
Hey, guys!
You fucking psycho!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's up, bro?
What the fuck you think, bro?
I'm a beekeeper.
I protect the hive.
Sometimes I use fire to smoke out hornets.
This is a multi-million
dollar operation, asshole.
Okay, so you can't come
up here, white knighting shit.
Will you stop his ass out, please?
I got it, I got it!
You fucking get it, you fucking get it!
Don't you feel really proud of yourself?
Mr...
Garnet?
Mr. Garnet.
I don't care if your
friends hear them or die.
The next call from
your little fishing scam.
This call center will make
a spark across these wires.
I've given all of the
gasoline fumes in here.
I promise you.
I think a lot of it won't be.
Guys, we might want to depart.
Flat white, oat milk, of course,
and extra chalice first, of course.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Did we get the otoro
and the onion? Yes, sure.
We did.
Finally, great.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
Hey, um, Mikaela.
Yes.
It came back, the whole thing?
Yeah, and it's like, I can barely
fucking move, it's all tweaked.
Oh, those are nice.
Those are the new bowls.
Yeah.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
What?
I'm in a meeting.
You said hit me on voice,
if there's an emergency.
Okay.
Well, uh... It seems we
had a disgruntled customer.
Uh, I just can't comprehend
why you're bothering me.
Just get in touch with the
attorney and start shoving back.
Well, you know, I don't think
that legal's gonna help much.
Okay, so what the fuck
is going on right now?
This dude just scrolls in.
Sam, we're stealing from people.
He just tears through.
All my security guys, like
fucking tissue paper, and, um...
And what?
And he burns the place to the ground.
Yeah, the call center's gone.
I'm standing here staring at a 30
million dollar building that's now, like...
Giant fucking ashtray.
Four people are gonna get out.
You're telling me that
this asshole burned the
entire building down and
dropped four fucking bodies?
Yeah, that's not exactly a
disgruntled customer, is it?
Who did this give me a name right now?
I don't have it.
All the other cameras in
the drive burned up in the fire.
He had a hat.
Oh, he had a hat.
Okay, I'm gonna hit you back, all right?
I gotta go big dog this shit for a minute.
Hey, can you talk to him for a while?
What? What? No, nothing.
I mean, if I had a friend who, like, had a
call center and someone burned it down,
maybe killed some people,
you could get him, right?
Get him?
Yeah, like disappear the problem. Come on.
Oh, Vietnam.
That's the way about my favorite.
You, you literally ran
the CIA and you're telling
me you can't just find
some guy in Massachusetts?
Listen, this sounds
like a job for the police.
I just need a name.
Well, you won't get it from me.
And you keep me a million miles away from
your metaverse mess lab or whatever it is.
Yep.
So check it out.
Daddy can't hold your hand on this one.
Uh, this is clearly some
kind of crime of passion,
spur of the moment, someone
snapped, like, whatever.
But, uh, we're gonna do some ascension
credentials, you're gonna log into our cloud,
and you're gonna look
at anyone connected
to the last few deals
you closed, all right?
Just, I don't know, start there.
And, like, what if I find this guy?
Then what?
You get a wrecking crew
together and you go good, Philazon.
I mean, come on, you're a
connected guy, right? You understand?
Yeah, no, I understand.
I, uh, I'll get it done.
It's called a day off.
Hey, you good?
Yeah, I'm great.
Why? I mean, you did
lose your mother yesterday.
Yeah.
What do you want, Wiley?
Are you leaving? There's a lift.
Remember United Daddy Group?
Are you sober
enough to drive? Yeah.
Give us a few seconds, thank you.
Where's mine?
It's an old cup for my car with
instant gas-dish and hot water.
Ew.
You want some?
No.
So, fire applied all the CCTV footage.
The reception and session
saw us in jacking this 40's,
manhandled security, and we
walked in with a couple gas cans.
This clown car saw
everything, but no one's talking.
They're all frequent pliers with
perjury, fraud, and side reviews.
Fucking scumbags.
I want ID's on all of them.
You know, this is just
the tip of a 20-spirit group.
Can I just have this
moment? Eloise Parker.
Yeah, I took her for
over 2 million yesterday.
She's, uh, she's black.
Widow just has a daughter in Boston.
I don't think this is it, but...
You said your boy has
an old-ass pickup truck.
That's him.
Then look at those.
What? Fucking beehive.
Yeah, Dickhead was talking about him.
I guess he's a, like, B-E lover.
You know what?
He breaks my shit.
You break his shit.
Fuck!
But where you at, B-Boy?
You fucking hiding, bitch?
Well, come here and fucking face us!
Hide, bitch, now!
Let's go!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Don't let me fucking
help you! Fuck.
No! I'm okay.
We, we, we can talk about this.
We can talk about this.
Does this point this out, me and you?
Fuck you!
So, help me understand,
because I'm a little confused.
What's the nature of your business?
I don't know nothing about no business.
So then why are people just
wiring you their entire life savings?
It must be your winning personality.
They got us some lawyers,
and they want to talk to them.
You know, this is a really
nice shirt, by the way.
Did you steal that out of a
casket, you dumb fucker?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Corona, if you're done shooting
all over this gentleman's civil rights,
can I speak to you for a moment?
It's a nice shirt.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm an asshole.
Oh, so you like fires?
Yeah, today I do.
Good, because today's your lucky day.
Apparently, your mother's
house is on fire, too.
And some other shit.
Wait, what?
Yeah, shit's on fire, let's go.
You good?
Me and you okay? Yeah.
That's a new one.
Where's Maggie?
Hey, Maggie?
I did? United Danica.
You know what he's handsome?
Are you okay? Yeah.
While I'm good, I'm good.
You think there's even
a remotest chance that
the dude can burn down
the magic out of you?
It's the same bad-wrenching
that's fought for your mother.
The V-keeper.
Plus my virginity in that barn.
Fucking shit!
The universe is gonna have to wait.
I'm gonna take this.
Yo, what's up, Leon?
This is the part where you
tell me what a good job you did
and I put you on a G6 to
Hawaii to chill for a week.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Danforth.
You fucked this up, are
you fucking crying right now?
I'm not, I'm not crying, I'm bleeding.
Bleeding?
What are you, why are you bleeding?
What do you mean bleeding?
My, my fingers?
Out of my right hand.
You can cut him off.
Okay, I'll go.
Go, go.
He, who the fuck is he?
Tell me who he is right now.
I, I don't know, the
fucking, fucking beekeeper.
Makes honey and it fucks with beehives.
He fucks with beehives?
What's he saying about bees?
I don't know, he said he was like
protecting the hive or something.
Oh, fuck, man!
What the fuck is this, you guys?
No, no, no, no, no, no,
go, go, go, go, go, go!
What, crypto?
I got fucking an F.D.
Any way, fucker?
No, don't fuck it, man.
Don't move.
That fucking can't
move! You fucking.
You have the pleasure of speaking with her.
Fuck you.
That's who.
You burned up a million
dollar fucking call center.
Now I'm gonna burn you down.
You haven't told me a name.
I told you my name.
It's fuck you, mister fuck you.
You better fucking remember it.
Because you don't burn
me down, I burn you down.
You understand me?
You are fucking important
that you cannot comprehend.
You sound young.
I bet you don't have a state punning.
I'm fucking 28 years old.
Why would I need that?
I'm about to show you.
And you say one guy did this?
Yep.
Killed seven armed
men without firing a shot.
And he said he was gonna kill me.
And this is your data mining
consumer service business, right?
Yes, something like that.
Pulling in nine million a month,
one office, I've got like 20.
Yeah.
The only thing you know about
him is he said he's a beekeeper.
Yeah, it's like his
whole brand or whatever.
Jesus.
What?
For someone who has
elevated fucking up into
an art form, this might
well be your Mona Lisa.
How did I fuck up? I don't know.
You've done something.
You've disturbed a beekeeper.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
So fucking what?
What I care if the guy keeps bees?
If a beekeeper says you're
gonna die, you're gonna die.
There's nothing I could do
or anybody else to stop it.
So, like, what do you even do here then?
What good are you?
I did 35 years of loyal
government service,
culminating as director of the
world's premier intelligence agency.
I could have done anything.
But I chose this job as
a favor to your mother.
Keep Danforth Enterprises safe.
Keep her reputation safe.
Her name safe.
My fucking name too,
all right? Oh, sit down.
I put up with you.
I put up with your tantrums.
Kept you out of the tabloids.
Kept you out of jail.
The endless stream of sex workers.
You're a drowning man.
Do you know that?
Hmm.
You're scared? Yeah, right.
I'm scared.
Terrifying.
So should you be.
Wallace, just tell me
what the fuck this guy is.
He's probably the last pair of
eyes that you're gonna sneer at.
Okay, listen.
Remember our favorite burning building?
United Data Group.
Guys who work there are hackers,
con men, fraudsters, et cetera, et cetera.
Guy who ran it, Garnet.
He's in the book.
He's a known mob associate.
He's missing, but I've
got PD chasing him down.
Okay, so I had some
analysts run some shit, and I
think I'm starting to get
the shape of the animal.
Dude, I think United Data Group
is one of several call centers.
So there's gotta be
like a central office that's
controlling all of them, and
that's what we gotta find.
This could be like a billion
dollar a year operation.
Hello.
Did you hear a single
word I just said? Yeah.
And?
Well, I'm just thinking you come
in here, hungover on your day off,
gain more yardage on this thing
than the whole squad has in two years.
Yeah, well, I fucked with my family.
What'd you get on Clay?
Your beekeeper? Yeah.
He's a ghost.
What?
Yeah, all I have is a birth
certificate and a social.
You guys never even had a bank
account or credit card flown on a plane.
I ran his prints through every
database I could think of. No hits.
That's bullshit.
This dude is former military all day.
No hits? I'm telling you.
Either he's never been printed
or Adam Clay doesn't exist.
Which is terrifying to me because
he's probably in a classified program.
Speciale Jumali.
Okay.
Let's go.
What? They found you.
Can I go now?
Let's go.
Shit.
Jessica.
I think you know why I'm calling.
You know I didn't do anything for you.
Anything.
For you.
Derek's scared shitless.
I've never seen him this scared.
Well, he's made his bet.
I'll give you a board seat on the holding
company that's another million a year.
Plus you promised you'd take care of him.
Look, I don't need that. I have enough.
So you got this? Yeah.
You have my word.
Wallace.
I still think of you.
Sometimes.
Why are you calling me on
to never call this limelight?
This is priority one, Janet.
Well, if it was priority
one, I would know about it.
Look, I'm heading downtown
to a POTUS briefing.
Just hear me out.
Now, you know who I work
for, don't you? Oh, yeah.
God help you, Wallace.
Exactly.
Well, Director Harwood,
my young friend, seems
to have caught the
unwanted attentions of...
I have no house to say this of a beekeeper.
Hey, Deb.
A beekeeper beekeeper? As in.
Well, that's not good.
No, it's not.
When's the body
count? Seven today.
Who is he making funeral arrangements?
I need help, Janet, not jokes.
Is that Garnett?
He's dropped to an old pickle.
Check this out.
Does this mean you've
taken pity on the old man?
So your problem?
He's retired from the program.
No longer active.
Well, that changes everything.
The current active
beekeeper is aware of the
issue and is going to be
taking things from here.
You can rest easy, old friend.
Oh, no, Janet.
The current active
beekeeper is a fucking
lunatic who should have
been removed months ago.
God help us now.
Get out of here!
Shit! Excuse me.
No clue.
No.
You've been a busy bee.
Yours mustn't be retired.
I'm assuming you're my replacement.
No, no, no.
I need your keys.
There's an issue.
Problem has not been solved.
Well, that is a surprise.
The beekeepers have studied the situation
and have decided to remain neutral.
How did he do that?
He was their man, for fuck's sake.
I'm sorry, Wallace.
You're on your own.
I thought you could fucking handle this.
I can't handle this! Thank you.
What you got for us, detective?
That's her vehicle,
registered to Anacet Landris.
The ATF will all en route
inbound to take care of it.
We're way cooler than ATF.
I'll show you why I called them.
That's a minigun.
They use those on military vehicles.
Do you know that puppy shoots
6,000 rounds a minute? I know.
Do you know that's 100
rounds a second? Yep, I know.
Did you know that you
know about it? Yes, I do.
It's because I minored in math.
Pretty smart guy.
Okay, then do you know who
Anacet Landris is? Yes, I do.
Go ahead and tell me.
Someone who doesn't exist in
commercial or government database.
Someone who's a ghost,
like our good friend Adam Clay.
Beekeeping for beekeepers.
Here's another reason that Anacet
Landris is like our good friend Adam Clay.
Do you know us
that way? Springfield.
Where the call center was torched.
And that way, we're Adam
Clay's headed? Austin.
Let's go.
How are you, my friend?
Good to see you so good.
Come on, make them alone.
Make them alone.
Don't play with those things.
They go off.
Sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
When I was sworn in as director, I was read
into programs I never imagined existed.
Well, there are programs
even I wasn't privy to.
Like the beekeepers.
The honey bee.
It's always had a special
relationship with humanity.
A sacred relationship.
No bees, no agriculture,
no agriculture, no civilization.
Our nation is not unlike
a beehive with its complex
systems of workers,
caretakers, even royalty.
If any of the beehive's complex mechanisms
are compromised, the hive collapses.
Someone long time ago decided that a
mechanism was needed to keep our nation safe.
A mechanism outside the chain
of command, outside the system.
It's one mission to keep the system safe.
Beekeepers are given all resources
empowered to act on their own judgment.
For decades, they have quietly
worked to keep the hive safe.
That is, until now.
It appears that a retired beekeeper
has gone on program and is
acting in what he mistakenly
believes is the hive's best interest.
Can't somebody just pick up a phone and
tell this yah-ho to stand the fuck down?
That's the one thing beekeepers don't do.
Stand down.
Not unlike bees themselves,
beekeepers keep working until they die.
He's basically one of us.
No, he's not like you.
You're tier one operators, former
SEAL team six, tell the group.
You are, in other words, pussies.
If you were in the same
room, he would kill you.
With enough of you, then
maybe you just might, in fact,
be able to kill him before
he accomplishes his goal.
And what would that be?
To kill his way to the top of the hive.
Mr.
Pettis, you should get your people moving.
Dude, bees are interesting
little shits, did you know that?
You know, they pollinate a bunch
of shit and we beat fuckers up.
Listen, some bees are queen
slayers, which will rise up and kill
their queen if she fails to produce
the right kind of male offspring.
Fascinating.
No.
Nope.
It's your turn.
Especially Jim Parker.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
What?
The deputy director is
flying up from DC to see us.
This is your fault.
No.
Here's another interesting factoid.
Thank you, fuck.
You know, I was getting sick of
enjoying my peaceful thoughts.
Sir?
Sir, this is Special Agent
Parker, Special Agent Wiley.
They'll be briefing you.
This is Deputy Director Burke and
Amanda Moon, your special counsel.
Mr. W. Director.
My colleague and I believe
that three major crime scenes
in our area are connected to
a single subject, Adam Clay.
He killed six people today
based on the extensive
use of trade graft and
the nature of his alias.
We believe that Mr. Clay is connected
to a classified program named Beekeeper,
a program that none of our partner
agencies seem willing to acknowledge.
Let's stick to what we
know, Special Agent Parker.
Yes, sir.
In any event, this individual is highly
capable and extremely motivated,
and we believe that he's on his
way to Boston, if not already here.
And we believe that this is his next target,
Nine Star United, which appears to be
the entity operating the regional call centers
like the one that Mr. Clay burned down.
Why is Adam Clay on this rampage?
He's protecting the hive, sir.
It's what beekeepers do.
I have enough to brief the director.
What's your ask?
My ask? Well, a
SWAT team, for starters.
Surveillance support,
additional agents, analysts.
That shouldn't be a problem.
Thank you.
Did that just happen? Yeah.
All right, everybody,
let's help us roll call times.
I'm getting ready for my dick to get hot
with some wonderful beautiful moments.
Stop with Phoenix. Where are we at?
Phoenix is off 201K.
201K for the fucking dick. I love you.
Show me. Where are we at?
It's down 93K, boss.
Now, you're a fucking
loser. You give me a
fucking headache, you
give me a fucking cancer.
New York, where do you have it?
I've got the New York City's up 65.
And now you're in New York.
We're all weapons front on entry.
We're ready. Come here and do it.
Power down, my federal friend. Power down.
The private security here under orders
of the governor. State Department certified
to carry weapons in all 50 states.
Feel free to call the
Highlight and I must verify.
You're not welcome here. Put the fuck up.
All right, boys, let's go.
Set up the perimeter outside.
We're both taking these loads of money,
money, money. We've got the money.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who the fuck are you? You can't be in here.
We're the guys keeping you alive.
Shut it down now.
Everybody, listen up. Anyone who's
not carrying a weapon, get the fuck out.
As soon as you be killed and live
or something, listen to me, my friend.
This place of Prince's
money, no one's shutting down.
Anybody, so much as puts
a phone down, they're fired.
I'm sorry to break it to you, but
the non's been dead for a while.
So I'm going to say this one last time.
Shut it down. The fuck are you?
I'm calling you a fucking boss.
Anybody call my boss?
I'll do that, and you'll be so fucked.
It's going to be beautiful.
Don't be shy. Come on.
You're about to park in the garage.
Closing lot. Still dating.
You want a body on comms,
watch. Delivery dock? Same deal.
Station in Aginbury too.
You sure there's no back
entrances in this place?
Hey, there's no other entrances.
Federal law enforcement
operation problems.
Move along, minimum
retreat at safe distance.
The other option, instead of
going in, is to smoke them out.
Excuse me?
I figured I'd give the
firefighters a break.
I put them through enough already.
But you say your name was?
Currently I'd go by Adam Clay. Trust me.
If it was a back entrance,
I would have used it.
I don't want to injure anyone
who's innocent or not involved.
But it is what it is.
Somebody detain this guy.
Stop!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Oh wow, it isn't the fucking
Golden Goose himself.
Sir, I got Captain Cape, and he
had told me he sent everyone home.
If we do that, we're walking
away from a lot of money.
Put him on.
It's for you.
Why are you fucking with
my business? Because Mr.
Westwild hired me to kick
some fucking bacon in his ass.
Mr. Westwild works for me,
which means that you work for me.
Now listen, that place is the
crown jewel of my kingdom.
I'm not going to let some crash test
dummy with a fucking gun fuck it up.
Mr. Pettis.
Didn't this character already burn
running a sentence to the ground?
Well, you know, they didn't have you.
And that's why.
So maybe you just do your fucking job
and don't tell me how to do mine, please.
We got it.
Copy that.
Let's fall out.
Set up a perimeter outside. Let's go.
Vile applause.
Let's say goodbye to our beautiful friends.
Bye bye, April.
Go join fucking Space Force.
You are beautiful, now get the fuck out!
Keep walking!
Bye bye, dear dad.
Bye, April.
I'm just going to stand up.
Yeah, you're welcome.
One time amnesty. Whoever doesn't want to
die this evening can in an orderly fashion.
Leave now.
No fucking way. It's not happening.
Anybody move, you're fired. No bonus.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, zero.
Okay?
Are you fucking nuts?
It's one of these pricks.
It's worth 30 to 40
million a year in practice.
So no one is shooting no guns.
Not a good day to drag
into some people into this.
These assholes, they're not innocent.
We're either one of us
to close that distance.
Some of them will get hurt.
Let's start with this prick right here.
Take me!
Paddis, we got a man down.
You know who you're working for?
I'm not in my fucking business.
I'm just the guy that called
me and there's a problem.
You are a problem.
Got them right up a problem.
Stop!
Stop! Stop! Fire.
Fire.
Dan, what the hell happened?
And he's dead?
Not dead, but we got our asses kicked.
Our guy? What do we know?
He's in the building.
I'm waiting for him to roll in.
I don't know what this guy is,
but nobody can do what he's done.
It's just a beekeeper.
But I do.
I'm not waiting.
Come on, wait.
No!
Come on, Wylie, keep up.
Fuck.
You done?
Everybody out!
We should take the stairs.
Smart.
Please, please don't kill me.
I'm just a middle manager.
I never had nobody.
I respect you more if you look people
in their eyes when you stop them.
Now, you're making a lot of money here.
Tell me where it's all going.
I don't know, man.
I know you're the middle man.
Who's above you? Don't kill me.
I'll torture you then kill you.
Come on, guys.
You got it.
Wylie!
Get your ass out here!
Yeah, well, I'm not an Olympian.
Make it stop.
You can make it stop.
You've stolen hundreds
of millions from people
who've done nothing but
work hard all their lives.
And she was an educator, mom, dedicated
to the whole life to help each other.
She was the only person
who took care of people.
Yesterday, she shot herself.
She took two million
from a charity she ran.
She was the only person
who ever took care of me.
Who and where is the Anzaloni?
Tell me who and where.
I hear this.
Look, these people are untouchable.
No, please, please!
I will!
Let me show you.
I told you they were untouchable.
Nobody's untouchable.
Sometimes when the hide is out of
balance, you have to replace the queen.
That man is the radio
responsible for your mother's death.
I believe you.
But we have laws for these things.
You have laws for
these things until they fail.
Then you have me.
Arrest him!
On your feet, properly,
you fucking head up!
I just fenced it under
a split glass window!
Get your fucking mouth!
No!
That's four kids.
I know. Three boys and a girl.
Wylie? Are you okay?
Yes.
You're okay? You're in LA.
Have you been hit?
I won't tell her if you've been hit.
No, I'm good, Mom.
Yeah?
Did you get him?
Did you?
No, he was tricking me.
Almost.
Okay.
I guess that's just evidence.
Can I borrow your
gun? Yeah, let's go.
Or me.
I want interviews with all of them.
We're gonna talk.
Get him out of here.
Wylie.
Do you mind if I ask you
a really boring question?
Do you actually prefer
the money or the power?
Ooh.
That's deep.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Excuse me.
Oh, God.
Would you excuse me for
a moment? Come upstairs.
You said these guys were the fucking best.
Why are they all dead?
You kicked the beehive
and now we have to reap.
The whirlwind.
Unless...
Unless, unless, unless,
unless fucking what?
Maybe now's the time to call your mother.
I'm paying you so much fucking money
and your advice is to call my mother?
He can't make his move on us if we're
in her proximity, can he? Her people.
You're a fuck.
You're scared and you want to
use my mother as a human shield.
Just call it, just call it, come on.
It's not a game.
Oh, it's all the game.
Come on.
Yes, Derek, what do
you want? Hey, Mom.
No, nothing, I was just, you know,
thinking about you, I miss you.
I was hoping to maybe see you this weekend.
I'm at the beach house, you're
welcome to join if you behave.
I would love to, hey, I'm actually
gonna, you know, get together
some of my tech homies and
stuff if that's, uh, that's cool with you.
Fine, no drugs, get Kelly the
details, love you, have to go.
Derek's joining me this weekend,
help me keep them sober.
Yes, ma'am, we're babysitting.
Madam President.
Hello.
Hello, good to meet you.
Sola, will you marry me?
Sola, thank you so much for coming.
Susan, I know this way.
Only right now.
Only right to meet you.
You don't have to do this, you know.
Why not let Clay do his thing?
Your mom is dead because of these people.
Wherever it's headed.
I swore an oath.
Can't stand by and watch it happen.
Even if he's right?
Even if he's right.
Apologies, damn plane was delayed.
What have you got?
We think we have a sense
of Mr. Clay's true intentions.
He seems to be following the money.
What money is that?
Usually it's from people
with no heirs, no family.
Nine Star United uses
data mining software to
identify these people and
then target their assets.
There's another company involved.
Sir, a company who is a
vendor to the intelligence
community and to the
Justice Department.
In fact, we use this
company's software in
this very office to
identify financial fraud.
Are you going to tell me the
name of this company? Ahem.
Danforth Enterprises. With
an annual revenue of $10
billion, founded and
operated by Jessica Danforth.
Who recently stepped down because she was
sworn in as President of the United States.
She self-financed
her campaign? Yeah.
None of that money was clean.
Who else knows this? Us three.
I have a really bad memory, sir.
Let's keep the circle small until I can
read the director and the attorney general.
Not a word of this to
anyone, understood? Yes, sir.
Mr. Clay, I see his kill
count is steadily rising.
In a beehive there is
something called a queen slayer.
It's a bee that will rise up and kill the
queen if she produces defective offspring.
I thought we were sticking
to the known knowns.
Right, yes, not that beekeepers exist,
but Mr. Clay does keep honeybees.
He admires their willingness to
sacrifice themselves for the greater good.
Our concern is that
Clay believes that Derek
Danforth is the defective
offspring of a queen.
Thereby Clay will strike at the heart of
the problem and become a queen slayer.
Adam Clay's next victim
is Derek Danforth's mother.
President Danforth, sir.
You have a blank check. Good luck.
Thank you.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is a private event. I'm going
to need to turn around, go away, fly.
I don't know if you're
of something or another.
We're good. We
have invites for you.
All right, you'll need to excuse
my partner who's recently
concussed and hasn't slept in
two days. We're on the access list.
We're good, boss.
Get the secret service
out of the house.
They don't want me. They're
cheating. They seem the best.
Uh, Mom's detail is not going to like that.
Well, if Mom's detail
gets in the way of what's
coming for us, they're
dead men, and so are we.
Tell them they can stay in the kitchen.
Yes, sir.
He has a little talent, doesn't he?
He's absolutely fucking terrifying.
Good man, but clearly not good enough.
Fuck you!
You're the best
I've got, huh? I do.
You're looking at me.
How was any of this my fault?
Wasn't your super secret CIA
data mining software supposed to...
I don't know, maybe you killed her
out, un-fucking-stop-bull-killing machine.
Don't you fuck with me, young man!
Any other life you'll be in jail...
Hey, this is the fucking vicky fuck!
Yeah, you know I killed one once.
Oh, you see?
Yeah, only because I was lucky.
And I'm fucking lucky.
Yeah, don't piss your pants, please.
My team will be our short people.
If anyone can knock this
guy's dick in the dirt, it's them.
Ain't that right,
money men? Yeah.
Madam President, he looks spectacular.
When the fuck are you going to tell
me what's going on, Wallace? Good.
Let's go.
Tell that guy to hurry up.
I want every man on
this street well to shut.
Gotcha.
I want every man on this
street to shut the fuck up.
Good.
Don't fuck your back, man.
Yeah.
Fix up.
Feed it up.
Get your head on it, little gentlemen.
I'm going to draw surprise.
Now.
Save the army.
Open your eyes, please.
Hey, when, uh, when did you get in?
What a surprise.
You didn't hear the giant marine
helicopter land on the front lawn.
I guess not.
Is this a nicotine or a carnival, right?
I wouldn't unless you want to
go talk with the machine elves.
Hey, you look fucking great, by the way.
Power just looks so good on you.
Doing blow on your father's desk.
God, why wish he was
still alive so I could kill him.
Stop picking your face.
Why does Wallace Westwad look nervous as a
burning cat? What have you done to the man?
I wouldn't know, Mother.
Well, he's there to
protect you if you'll let him.
You're a good-looking kid.
You really are, you know that?
What does that mean?
It means that God doesn't
give with both hands.
Okay, I love you too, Mom.
Let it go, run the free world.
Don't burn him down.
Finally, look.
Oh shit.
And of course, it looks
like she wants to throw up.
Mother Biden, bad vibes.
You got caught right in dirty.
What have we done?
Are you fucking with crypto
at all right now? It's gonna pop.
I think they're minting next week,
so just hit me up on that stuff.
Okay.
I'll connect your wallet.
Yeah, I'll roll my song.
Speak to you when I'm deprived.
Uh, who's this?
Jackson Perk, he's number two with the FBI.
Have a seat.
Oh, I'm cool. I was saying, what is it?
Is it going to ambush or something?
This feels weird. I don't like it.
No, you'll sit.
I'll sit.
Kelly, would you give us a moment?
It's okay, ma'am. I can take notes.
I need you to step outside.
The deputy director has
flagged his concerns about some
uncomfortable things happening
inside the family company.
Why?
Uncomfortable things about
the source of my campaign funds.
Sound serious? What's up?
Deputy director.
Mr. Davenport, are you
familiar with United Data Group?
United Data Group? Yeah, yeah.
I invested in that.
I invest everywhere. I mean, there's,
it's everywhere. It's very diverse.
How about a nine-star United?
Yeah, that was, that's more
of like a consulting-type role.
It's the blockchain issues, and
you might think, don't do that.
What do you know about a
classified, algorithmic, data-mining
software package developed by
the intelligence community? He's here.
All stations, targets in the building,
east wing, can be everything you got.
He's in the house.
Assault team!
Saddle down!
Move, boys! Move, boys!
Break, break! Packages in the house!
Level three, site four!
Blue over blue, you see him!
You fucking get him!
Hey! Put your fucking hands up!
Now turn the fuck
around! He's outside.
Target's outside.
Let's get this fucking guy!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
See him? Negative.
Hey!
Test run!
Now!
On your knees!
Place your fingers behind your head.
Down!
On your knees!
Now! Do it, now! Pinky bar.
God's right there.
You aren't shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, take your step back.
I'm putting this asshole's
brains on the lawn.
What are you doing? Is
that him armed? I'm not.
As long as this motherfucker's
bleeding his arm.
You're not fucking executing him!
Nice crowd you're on.
Watch me.
Hey, what the fuck is going on?
Is it to be or not to be?
Isn't that the bloody question?
I think I'll take...
to be.
Riley?
Yeah, you good? Yeah.
Get off the roof!
Fucking lie!
Talk to me, people. I need news.
He's here!
No, no!
You're all seated!
You're behind space!
Why are you
waiting? Take it easy.
Take it easy.
Hold your hands,
guys! Hold this off.
You understand.
You did this, right?
You broke the rules.
You corrupted an imperfect
but functioning sister.
I was just trying to get
you in your office, Mom.
How did you get elected?
I was going to win with
or without your help.
We were already rich.
Your father built an empire.
Yeah, and you were gonna fucking
break it up into pieces and sell it off.
But in the name of public
service, because I care,
I want to leave a better world.
Okay, right.
Yeah, because you hate
the fact that being the
president is just like an
endless cocktail party.
You realize that you were behind in
15 of 20 counties you needed to win.
15 of 20 counties.
I taught CIA software to
hunt money and not terrorists.
You didn't hear that.
You elected because of me.
And you know that.
Yeah, I know it.
Everyone knows it.
Now I know where the money came from.
And all the people you heard.
Okay, whatever.
It's computer data, Mom.
Somebody has to have their fucking feet
on the ground to actually get shit done.
You understand that?
Mom, the wolves are at
the fucking door right now.
What are you gonna do
to fix this? Tell the truth.
The fucking.
..
What does that even mean?
Tell the fucking truth!
You have an entire
building full of PR people
that are gonna choose
the right way forward.
That guy who's coming
to kill us, that beekeeper,
I'm telling him the truth
about what you did, Derek.
Then I'm telling the entire nation,
and if it costs me
everything, I'll stop you.
Get the hell out of here!
You're just a man.
No, no.
No! No! Thank you.
Looks like a tornado came through here.
What's your plan here, huh?
You're gonna tell this
guy the fucking truth
and hope that he spares
you and kills me instead?
No, Derek, I'll tell him the
truth because it's the truth.
It's gone far enough,
you proved your point.
Beekeepers live for the good of society.
Retired.
This is personal.
All the more reason to stop.
Go back and live a quiet life,
making honey for your neighbors.
That's all I wanted.
The neighbor's dead.
I know, I'm sorry.
But do you live in the real world,
or just protect it?
What does it matter to you how
presidents come to be elected? It doesn't.
Well, what does matter to you?
Right and wrong.
It's not fashionable.
I believe there's good in the universe.
Yeah, well, we agree.
I mean, that's my view.
Till the downfall family bought you,
you would stop pretending.
We wouldn't need beekeepers
if it wasn't for men like you.
Don't do that.
So you might want to step back.
No.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I'm sorry, I can't do that.
Now have a seat.
No, fuck the truth, man.
The truth.
Wait, wait, wait,
can you put that down here first?
Jesus!
That's fucking real right there.
Wait, no!
Drop the weapon! Drop it!
You decide who you work for.
For the law.
Or for justice.
Hold this.
Goodbye, mom.
No! No! I want my.
..
No! I want my.
No!
Uploaded by sookantv.com